Yuriko, here we go.
Yes.
I'll measure the height.
5'6 and a half.
The top.
The height is 8.
Please.
Let's go, Mako.
Here we go.
The mayor's office is still here.
Excuse me.
I'm going in there too.
Oh, okay.
I can't even organize the passers-by.
You idiot.
Excuse me.
Hey!
Excuse me, can you move?
No!
Oh, you want to see?
You're so annoying.
I'm sorry, I'll go this way.
Are you okay?
Yes, around there.
Here we go.
Reifu.
Yes.
It's still in.
Shikano!
I'm sorry, you did it on purpose, didn't you?
No, I didn't.
The support is for everyone.
Now, please take a look.
I'm sorry, I'm filming right now,
can you move over there?
Well, good job.
Good job.
Eat the vegetables properly or you'll die.
So, what's going on?
I'm moving out.
Where?
It's a secret.
You can't just not know the address of the teacher.
I won't let you in the next room.
I know that.
Women are so stubborn.
Stop it.
It's fine.
You're splitting up.
Are you mad?
We split up.
I don't date girls like you.
Then what are we?
We're both superiors and subordinates.
Ouch!
I'll post it on social media.
Can you do that even after you're done with your career?
You're that kind of person too.
I can't take a good picture of you talking like that.
Listen.
We have to stay away from the common sense.
You're a little...
Excuse me.
Hey.
What are you doing?
Who's driving?
Thank you everyone!
It was Shinji!
That's right!
If you can, please fold your feelings and ask!
Thank you very much!
What is it?
I'm finally out.
You've got the job offer, right?
I'll forgive you if you do.
Please don't call me anymore.
There's no one.
But...
I can't.
Die.
It's a sea.
It's the sky.
Do you earn money by climbing a mountain pass?
It depends on the person.
I'm already a hard worker.
That's tough.
I can't help it. I'm the only one who can do it.
What kind of photos do you take?
I take pictures of landscapes and people.
Are they interesting?
Don't you think of them as delicious or nostalgic?
They look delicious?
I don't think so.
You want to take pictures of them.
I'll call the police.
What?
I'll call the police!
Are you a child?
Mom!
I know, I know.
So?
Your wife found out about the cheating and kicked you out of the house.
Did you get cheated by another woman?
I was looking at you.
So I'm going to train you.
Before you become a citizen.
You need a lot of experience to become a cameraman.
It hurts.
Thank you very much.
Wait, wait, wait.
Shall we call the driver?
Is it okay around Kowahara-kun?
Of course.
It's really good.
I'm going to be alone for a while.
It's good.
I have a project for you.
What?
Yeah.
Let's shoot it next time.
Is that true?
Yeah.
Here, have the same amount.
Okay.
It's a magic.
Magic.
I'll give you a Zitonic.
Yes.
It's okay.
What is it?
Are you her boyfriend?
Have you gotten involved?
Have you done it?
It's a little...
I'm coming again.
I'm going to drink with you.
I know your picture is boring.
I'm going to puke.
What?
I'm sure you have sex.
I think so.
I'm going to puke.
You are a fool.
Do you want to be a comedian?
Do you want to be Kamitama?
I will never be like you.
Stop it.
Stop it?
You are not a child to be told.
I'm going to puke.
Stop it.
Hey.
I'm going to puke.
Doctor.
Yes.
Mr. Joe.
I'm going to call a rest stop.
Yes.
I'm leaving.
No.
Let's go.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Wait.
Go, go, go!
Is that monkey a monkey?
He was a quadruped for a while.
Do you have a kid like that?
I saw him on some TV show.
I was the best in the race.
Then I started to look like a monkey.
I was happy because everyone liked it.
That's why my nickname was monkey.
Christ!
You're a little...
...tough.
Shut up!
I said that in monkey language.
What's that?
I'm a glasses.
Why?
Since I was little,
I've had really bad eyesight.
I've been wearing glasses all the time.
Now I only wear contacts.
What happens if you take off your contacts?
I can't see anything. It's dangerous.
I'm like, where are my glasses?
What are you talking about?
I'm serious.
Let's show them our 4th grade.
Are you sure?
I'm sure.
Uki, uki, uki, uki, uki.
I got something.
What is this?
It's a fire.
Really?
I wonder if it's okay.
It's amazing.
It's impossible.
It's a secret.
Are you okay?
Let's try it.
It's a fire.
There's a fire.
This?
It's good.
Cheers!
Want to see?
Yeah!
I like it.
It feels nostalgic.
Really?
The person who took the photo is very unique.
It's like you.
What kind of person?
Kind and lonely.
Why?
It reminds me of my childhood.
Thank you.
I've never heard that before.
Ororo?
What?
Are you crying?
Are you drunk?
Yeah, I'm drooling.
Yes.
Wait, wait, wait.
I'm surprised.
Are you okay?
I was here when you did the quadruple-throwing.
Wait, wait, wait.
I'm sorry.
Wait.
Let's go over there.
Over there?
Okay.
Wait.
I'm drunk.
Okay, okay, okay.
Thank you.
Here.
Oh, my God!
I'm sorry.
Good luck!
I'll do my best!
Let's go!
Music!
Music?
Something, something.
First.
Good.
It's okay, one more time!
That hurts.
How long does it take?
I don't know, I lost my mind.
I see.
Good job.
This is the worst.
Two months of Matsuba.
How much did you earn?
This much.
We don't have a job to think about.
But I'm practicing the art I can do in Matsuba.
I got injured and got in a wheelchair.
If I had to force myself to get in a wheelchair,
I'd be a first-class civil servant.
Seriously?
That's how it is, Japanese.
I'll remember that.
How are you doing lately?
I don't know.
I got fired from my part-time job.
Oh, and I'm a three-month pensioner.
You're still a jerk.
Yeah.
How about practice?
That's fine.
Good.
I'm not good at this.
I want to be like Kotaro.
You have to keep going.
If you give up, that's the end of it.
Yes.
Shinji.
Yes?
Can I borrow some money?
Did you hear what Kotaro just said?
I was just kidding.
What the hell?
Welcome.
Sorry for being late.
I'm Kanuro.
I'm Yuriko Shika. Nice to meet you.
You're more beautiful than I thought.
Cheers.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you too.
I'm asking you out of the blue.
Can I borrow some money?
You're a senior.
Let me go.
What's that?
Gin Tonic.
Gin Tonic?
Yes.
I got a new one.
I'm going to get it.
Kotaro, you're late.
I'm not injured.
Hey.
What's wrong with you?
It's none of your business.
You're lying.
I see.
I'm glad.
Nice.
By the way, the contest for photo magazines that I published the other day has been cancelled.
I see.
Yeah.
Next time.
I see.
But you're still a coward.
You'll get stronger over and over again.
Right?
I know.
It's kind of cold today.
Hey!
Are you okay?
It'll get warmer soon.
I'm scared if Shinji's not here.
What do you mean?
It'll get colder if you're alone.
I wonder if I can come back here again.
You'll be fine, Yuriko.
You'll be fine.
I hope so.
When you're done, check and refill the water.
Okay.
Don't eat too much of the washing.
You've been waiting for so long for a part-time job.
You only put me in the right spots.
To feed him who has no income.
Do I look like a person who likes to eat?
I wonder.
I'm a private store.
A private store?
I want to open a photo store.
Oh, I see.
Yuri-chan is a real-time cameraman.
I mean, he's still an assistant.
I envy people who have dreams.
I don't have anything I want to do.
I think I'm just a man.
I'm just a man.
Are you?
Men are idiots.
It's fun to bully.
Miho-san is amazing.
It's not good to drink in the morning.
Today is a holiday.
Yesterday was the day before.
Is that so?
Hey, are you practicing properly?
I am.
While drinking?
It stinks.
Hey, if you keep drinking like that, you'll become a tourist and become a beggar.
It's okay.
My father was like that, too.
I'll give you a light.
What?
Nothing.
Please look forward to tomorrow!
See you again!
Thank you!
What's wrong?
Gag!
Hey.
Are you serious?
I thought I'd get hurt this time.
I'll be a real man for a year,
and I'll have to fight big here.
No.
You're so cool.
Right?
I'm proud of you.
But...
I'm in trouble.
I don't have enough money.
You're here again.
No, I'm serious this time.
What's wrong?
That's right.
I've collected 100 yen at the ryokan.
But I can't contact the person who will give me 50 yen.
If you have 50 yen, you can pay me.
He's still a minor.
I've been through a lot,
but he's cold.
I can't rely on anyone else.
Only you.
There's no way.
I don't have that kind of money.
I'll ask for it.
No, no.
I can't.
I'm almost like a friend to her.
Please.
My dream.
I can't.
I can't do it.
Please.
Please sit down.
I'm not doing anything.
Hey, it's weird that you want to do something for people when you're not doing anything.
Please.
I can't do it.
If my friends are active, it will be a stimulus for me.
To be honest, I've been feeling down lately.
But when I heard about Kotaro, I thought I had to do it properly.
I was surprised.
It's okay. I've never been lied to by that person.
Then it's okay.
Do you want to go for a drink?
No.
What's wrong with you?
Come on.
Hello.
Are you really angry?
Let's go!
What are you doing? I'm going!
Hey!
Come here!
I said stop!
I'm going!
Let's go!
One more time!
You're getting taller and taller!
I didn't see anything.
It's boring!
Study more!
Study! Study! Study! Study! Study! Study!
Hi!
Hey, Shin-chan.
What's up?
Good work.
Oh, Shin-chan.
What was it like today?
Not good.
Shin-chan.
What?
I don't know.
I asked Kotaro-san for some money.
What?
I heard that he stole money from everywhere and flew away.
He's a man of honor, right?
That's not true.
What do you mean, a man of honor?
He's got tickets, too.
What?
I asked Kotaro-san for some money, too.
And he never gets any money.
When did you contact Shin-chan recently?
I don't know.
I don't think I've talked to him lately.
I wonder if it's hard to connect because I'm overseas.
When is it?
It's hard for both of us, but let's do our best.
Cheers!
Welcome.
What's wrong?
I came to see how you're doing.
I have to contribute to the sales.
I went to the store today.
There's nothing to do before contributing to the sales.
It's fine.
It's not good.
Kiyo-san, gin tonic.
Yeah!
It's fine.
I'm sure you're drinking at a store where a lot of people work.
Who paid for this month's rent?
If you have time to do useless things like Daidouge,
work hard and pay me back my money.
What?
Give it back.
Chihagengka is the best!
Hehehe
Yes
Do you know that the electricity bill for the time zone at midnight is cheap?
In short, the idea is to store the cheap time zone electricity in a built-in battery
and use it during the day
Yes
Sunlight panel
Sunlight panel is...
Please wait a moment
Cute
Oh, sorry, I want you to go
Catch it, catch it
It's silver
Yes
Oh, sorry
This is the price
Yes
Oh, it's beautiful
Really?
Yes
Beautiful
Then, can you remove the button little by little?
Yes
Yes, yes, yes
Little by little
Oh, nice
The collarbone is beautiful
Really?
Yes
Nice
Oh, cute
Cute, cute, cute
Hey.
Yes?
The last girl today...
Was she okay?
Yes, she was.
She said she's going to have surgery next time.
And she sent me an email saying she wanted to leave a clean body before the wound.
It depends on the person, but...
Well...
It's more fun than having a model who doesn't get along with you.
Yes.
Well...
I changed my mind after seeing her in person.
I'm glad.
You want to have a shot too?
I don't have a body that I want to remember.
Don't say that again.
No, really.
You should have taken it when you were young.
No, it's okay.
It's okay.
I said it's okay.
I won't call you again.
Okay.
I got it.
Bye-bye.
Idiot.
Idiot!
Yo.
You're not used to the suit.
I've always been free.
How's Yuri?
She's busy lately.
She doesn't come to the store.
I don't know, but I guess so.
She's late for work.
What about the Daido game?
I'm taking a break.
It's none of your business.
You look like you're bored.
Isn't there anything interesting?
You want to have sex with me?
Is that interesting?
I don't know.
Are you sure?
I just wanted to do it.
Anyone is fine.
If it's a human being, then it's a human being.
What are you doing?
It's hot.
Ouch!
cute
Tada!
Miho-san, are you okay?
Yeah.
It's painful.
I'm going.
I'm so nervous.
Are you nervous?
Just a little bit.
At first, everyone is very nervous, but please relax.
Relax your shoulders.
I'm going to take a picture.
How long have you been doing this?
8 months.
Are you a boy or a girl?
I'm a boy.
Really?
You're younger than me.
I'm a little nervous.
I'm nervous.
You're a little nervous.
I'm not nervous.
I'm nervous.
Are you a boyfriend?
I just took a picture.
Well,
I have a boyfriend,
but I don't know much about him.
Next, please lean on the corner of the floor.
Are you okay?
Good job.
Thank you for your hard work.
I'll go ahead and wash the dishes today.
Yes.
How is it?
Perfect.
Perfect?
Are you doing well?
I'm doing well.
Okay, I'll do my best.
Please enjoy it.
Oh, that's right.
Thank you for your hard work.
Have a nice day.
I'll go.
I forgot something!
Wait a minute!
Not there! Not there!
Toilet! Toilet!
Come on!
This way! This way!
What's this?
I told you not to contact me anymore.
No.
I heard you were with Aika.
I thought I'd say hello.
Joe and I have nothing to do with each other.
We're still students.
And...
She's my ex-girlfriend.
I heard that.
You're not good at business.
Yuriko!
Oh, please go home.
I saw your photo in the office.
You have a good sense.
But you said you were an assistant again.
You're a cameraman.
What's wrong with you?
Just take it.
That's what it means to be a professional.
Don't say that.
I'm retiring.
The model I was looking for...
...has been exposed on Twitter.
She's ruined my job.
I'll be on the news tomorrow.
Seriously.
But that's how it is.
I know I wanted a chance to sleep with you.
But I couldn't help it.
I know everything about you.
No, you don't.
But I learned something.
You told me that you couldn't depend on anyone to make your dream come true.
You told me that you had no choice but to do it yourself.
What a boring woman.
I'm cold.
Don't come to see me again.
I've decided not to come back.
I see.
You'll do your best.
I loved your hand.
It was thin, soft, and smooth.
I loved it the most in the world.
Wait, what?
Sorry.
Well,
I won't see you again.
Here you go.
Is this your first time?
Yes, I don't know anything.
You're so close.
I'm embarrassed.
I have a budget for the photo exhibition I recently did.
I'll bring it.
Please wait.
Please open it.
Thank you.
I hope it goes well.
Thank you very much.
I'm getting healthier.
I think I can study a little.
You're a beauty major, right?
I'm a beauty major.
Why did you know?
Me too.
I'm so happy.
You're going to get into the budget?
I'll see about that.
But I have so much to do that I'm going to puke.
How is this?
Isn't it good?
Yuriko is a genius!
How about you, Shinji?
What?
You did the Daidogei for the first time in a while, right?
How was it?
It was nothing compared to the practice.
You don't have to pay me back.
I'll take care of it myself.
I'll pay you back.
I'll pay you back no matter what.
Really?
It's been a while. You must be busy.
I asked you to come, but I'm sorry I can only work three times.
No problem.
I'm free anyway.
I'll drink sometimes.
Then, would you like a beer?
Sure.
Kiri-chan.
Yes?
I'm with Shinji.
With what?
Sex.
You're so bad at this.
You should train more.
What? Are you mad?
What?
You're sleeping too.
With another man.
You're not sleeping!
See you later.
One, two, three.
I did it!
What the hell is this?
I didn't do it.
It's cold.
Were you awake? What about work?
I'm off.
Where were you?
At the hotel.
You want me to pay for the power?
What if I did?
I'm sorry.
I'm a fool, a lazy person, I drink a lot, I have no money, I'm not good.
Yeah, that's right.
I know! I know, but I can't help it.
What is this?
I don't want to borrow it.
It's fine.
I'll return it.
Let's break up.
Us two.
What's wrong with this money?
It's my work money.
Are you serious?
I'm having a hard time with you.
You're working hard for your dream, but I'm not working hard at all.
You have talent, but I don't have any.
Stop playing the big game.
I'm the same as Kotaro.
I may have been looking for an opportunity to escape.
I'm just doing what I do now.
I wonder if it suits me.
I'm so happy to be full every day.
Is that okay?
No.
Are you going to hang out with Miho next time?
No way.
That's the only way you can do it, right?
What kind of a person are you? You're making me mad!
Let's break up.
I don't mean to be in a relationship.
Well then, I'll get rid of the dandruff.
Yuriko!
Yes!
I have a question.
What should I do?
Well...
The place is fine here, but...
The flowers are on the right side.
Please.
Do you need help?
No, no, it's okay.
Don't worry.
It's okay.
There's a light around here.
You can't touch the photos.
I'll bring Ame-chan.
Thank you.
You're so nice.
Yes.
Thank you.
I managed to make it somehow.
Yes.
Thank you very much. You have helped me.
Here too.
Yes.
Thank you very much.
I did my best to help you.
Finally, it has become in shape.
What?
Please give this to Shinji.
Yes.
See you.
Yuriko Shika's photo exhibition.
It's boring.
Do you like it?
I thought the title and the pictures were perfect.
Thank you.
Baba-kun!
Can you do the overtime for me?
You said you'd be early today.
Really?
But if you go home, no one else will be here.
But...
I'll leave it to you for 30 minutes.
As you say.
Yes.
I'm sorry.
I'm not being stupid.
Yes.
I'm sorry.
Sorry, I have 30 minutes left.
The next person is late.
I don't have time. I can't go on.
I told you at the beginning.
There's a overtime here.
But today...
Oh, right.
Then you can go home.
You don't have to come back.
I'm fired.
It's natural that you're going home.
You're such an idiot!
I'm going to end this boring lecture!
It's over!
Don't you dare take a picture of me!
Don't you dare do that, you bastard!
What are you doing?
I'm going to take a picture of you!
Shut up!
Thank you very much.
You're a boyfriend of a woman.
You're not a man.
You're a man.
What?
It's okay.
Your boyfriend didn't come, did he?
Well, that's fine.
I'm sorry.
2 hours late
5 minutes?
I was waiting
I felt like Shinji would come
Wait, wait!
Wait!
I broke up with Miho.
I want to apologize to her.
You're a little bit disturbed.
Calm down.
I understand.
Thank you.
This is the one I took.
I put them together.
It's nice.
I miss the past.
I feel like it's a long time ago.
You know, I've decided something while I was running to the venue.
What?
What if I meet Yuriko?
What if you meet her?
I want to try Daido-ge again.
See, Kotaro-san. He left saying he was going to Ejinbara.
Then I'll follow Kotaro-san's lead and do some overseas training.
That's good.
That's really good.
What?
I don't know, but I'm so happy.
Ororon.
I don't know how many years it'll take,
but I...
I...
I have to do my best for her.
Ororon.
Why are you crying?
I don't know.
I can't do this.
It's not a bad idea.
It's not a good idea.
You're not a bad idea.
Kotaro?
Hey!
You idiot! You're gonna get a bone marrow again!
What are you doing?
We were worried about you!
I really wanted to go.
But before I left, Tamaki took money and a ticket and went somewhere.
I'm a victim too.
I can't help it.
If I always seem to be doing well, I'm always in the way of someone.
And she went with the real Kotaro.
To Ejinbara.
What are you talking about?
By the way...
Who are you?
You're Kotaro's fake.
The real Kotaro is not a lame man like this.
Did you live around here before?
Yes, it's been five years.
I'm a bad boyfriend from Daidougei.
This town hurts!
What's he doing?
Is he still working overseas?
Well...
He's definitely drinking again today.
He's definitely drinking again.
He's the worst.
He's really the worst.
I'll take a picture.
Please.
Tera-chan, you look so cool.
Thank you.
You've been a really good man since before.
I did it.
Try to pull that.
Here I go.
I feel like Hawaii.
Tera-chan, can you run like a monkey?
What's that?
Just run.
I can't.
I'm not saying you can't.
Just try to your limit.
I'll try.
You used to be such a crazy person.
Here I go.
Please.
It's good.
I'm a real man.
You did a great job today.
Really?
You're the best.
Please sit down.
Okay.
I'll start from the side.
You're a real man.
You're a good man.
Be confident.
You did a monkey.
You did a good job.
You're a good rider.
There was a person who was shooting a big mountain pass over there.
It's a foreign country.
Really?
Are you going to see it?
The sun is setting.
Work, work!
Yes.
I wanted to go see it.
There was Hawaii.
There is no way!
Let's go.
I will go!
I can go!
Good luck!
This is a mess.
It's really dangerous.
It's dangerous to talk.
Applause!
It's hard to get off.
Yes!
Until the end!
It's really a mess.
I want you to be satisfied and go home.
I will turn more than usual.
I will go!
Yes!
I did it!
What?
I want to go more.
It's dangerous.
I can't go that far.
I will go more.
That's it.
Yes.
I will go.
Let's go.
Yes!
Let's clap!
I will do it if you do it.
Applause!
It's late.
What?
What did you do?
I'm in pain.
Did you stop the snow?
Applause!
It's a future story.
I can't believe it.
It's amazing.
Let's go.
It's a picture of the sky.
It's amazing.
I'm sorry.
Are you hungry?
I'm hungry.
You are cute.
Yes, this is it!
What a nice customer!
Shin-enji!
You too!
This is my story. Don't you watch?
Yuriko, let's go!
Okay!
I'll measure your height.
I'm 5'6.5.
Your height is also...
8'0.
Please.
Let's go, Mako.
Here we go.
Nice.
That's right.
Let's look at this side.
Ref!
Good.