LAST SUMMER...
Did you drink alcohol that evening?
Yes.
-How many?
Two or three glasses.
-Two? Or three?
Three.
How many boyfriends have you had this year?
Less than ten? More than ten?
Less than ten.
And how many did you sleep with?
You can sleep with whoever you want.
As long as it was with consent,
no one will judge you.
As a minor, your hearing is closed,
but I need to know everything. How many?
Seven.
Is that a lot?
-That's not the point.
The opposing team will portray you as one
slut who fucks everything that comes with it.
And claim you agreed.
That is not true.
I know that.
That's how the defense plays it.
In court
victims often become suspects.
But don't worry...
...the judges are used to that
and know how to distinguish.
Whatever you hear, stay calm.
And tell when you are interrogated
always the truth.
Does mom really have to be there?
No pictures. She is underage.
Are you satisfied with the verdict?
-We were hoping for more.
But at least my daughter will be
recognized as a victim.
We are going to process this nightmare
to recover.
Girls, isn't daddy
to the riding school with you?
Rebecca called. Théo has been arrested.
You mean it.
-As usual...
...can't explain anything to his mother properly,
so I prefer to go there.
What has he done now?
-Arguing with his math teacher.
He was suspended for two days,
she said...
...but now it turns out he's him
punched him in the mouth.
Shit.
-So he files a report.
I can just about do it
catch the train to Geneva.
Can you bring the girls?
Girls, come. Get in quickly.
I'll take you myself eventually.
Thank you.
Théo is coming to live with us.
-That sucks.
Pierre wants a bond with his son,
this is the chance.
But he's a problem child, right?
Speaking of problems. Just hold on.
You take him as planned,
or you say no and I look for a babysitter.
But you're not going to mess with you
dull head as soon as it becomes too difficult for you.
Mina...
-Nothing Mina.
Come, your aunt is here.
She will be thrilled to see you.
Lucas.
I didn't kiss daddy.
-Go ahead.
I'm nervous.
My heart, a kiss here.
And a kiss there.
Come, sit down.
Please stay seated there.
Don't move and don't talk.
After your aunt, I have two more customers.
-Cool dragon you have.
Got it from daddy?
What a sweetheart, your father.
I'm going to put it among my treasures.
Shall I take him with me?
to play with the girls?
Then you can join us for dinner
when you come to get him.
No, but sweet of you.
I can't see that jerk anymore.
He doesn't understand that I work...
...even if the work is worthless.
Hello, Theo.
Hi.
-I came to bring you things.
Wouldn't you like to leave them swinging?
Look, you have plenty of closet space.
Okay?
-Cool.
You've grown up so much.
-Yeah, that's cool.
One more year and then plea.
-Plea?
This is a goddamn hole.
Yeah, it's a bit remote for a teenager.
There's a train going. You get used to it.
Good...
But why wasn't he here?
-Because he lived with his mom.
Do you want also?
-Why?
That's why, Miss Why.
Because that's just how it was.
We had lunch without you.
I do not eat meat.
-Mom, I'm going to get Théo's present.
But I would like coffee.
To wake up.
Open it.
I made it at school.
For your key.
And I made the wrapping paper.
-Oh yeah?
How sweet.
Very nice. Thank you so much, Angela.
Thanks, Serena.
What beautiful paper you have made.
I understand, but...
Listen, it's unacceptable
that you train the matter this way.
If you take off your administrative glasses
you would agree with me.
It concerns a girl of 13
that has been waiting for centuries.
Her mother is dead, she is in a home,
far from the only parent she has left.
What's taking so long?
And now you fall.
-And yet I didn't fall.
Because I'm small.
In real life you have to fall.
Then again.
That was an osotogari.
That hurts, doesn't it?
I'm very good at judo.
I strangle all the boys.
Mom, we were playing.
That was amazing. What is that?
It's completely loose. Oh, no, not.
It's hell.
Instead of thanking me
that I give 700 people a job...
...they start nitpicking.
They don't want to understand...
...that I own the company's profit
invested in the holding company.
What was in the left pocket
went into the right pocket.
If you don't invest in innovation,
you will go down.
But no, what interests them is
the right pocket. The left pocket doesn't matter.
It's simple. I'm going for a tax audit
applications from the holding company and all branches.
Then they will see that I don't have a cent
stole from the tax authorities.
And then they just stop their recovery
up their asses.
Come on, it's late. We are going to sleep.
You're tired, you can't do it anymore.
Don't you think I'm an old fart sometimes?
Never.
Théo thinks I'm an old fart.
And he lets me know that too.
Yesterday he said I have the girls
adopted to ease my conscience.
Because I wasn't there for him.
Really and truly?
Where does he get it from?
He's a mean brat.
He says I could have been their grandfather.
He's not always like this.
He gets along well with the girls.
They're crazy about him.
In any case, that is positive.
We're just old farts to him.
Wouldn't you rather sleep?
You're exhausted.
When I was 14...
...I was secretly in love
to a friend of my mother's.
I thought it was so elegant.
And at the same time
I described in my diary...
...relentless are wrinkles.
His thin, parchment skin.
As if he were already dead.
Like he was disintegrating.
Relentless.
Towards death.
I was disgusted.
And at the same time I was fascinated.
Do you know how old he was?
33.
I saw him as an almost-corpse.
Just think.
And how do you see your old man?
I'm a gerontophile, you know that.
A body that has lived and not
has more the firmness of youth...
...makes me emotional.
I find that moving.
I'd rather not have you smoking in the house.
And I'd rather not want this either.
-It's not hash. Be happy.
Théo, we do our best
to make you feel at home here.
It would be cool
if it didn't come from one side.
Okay what?
-Understood. Let me, I'm busy.
By which?
-With work.
Oh yeah? What are you working on?
Let me, I said. You distract me.
I don't believe a word of it
that you work.
You don't do anything except play games
and I know what to look at.
That's my problem. It'll be fine.
It'll be fine? What does that mean?
You have exams at the end of the year.
It's hell here. Get lost.
To begin...
-Give it back, dammit.
Who do you think you are?
That's mine. Are you crazy or something?
Here.
I have an hour and a half.
-Better than nothing. I never see you, Mimi.
And your stepson?
-He detests me, but that's okay.
What is this?
I'm going to call Pierre.
Pierre, we've been broken into.
I do not know. They're stuck
forced open the garden doors.
You should see the living room.
Yes, I'll call the police.
My bag has disappeared from the hall.
I haven't seen anything else yet.
Yes.
What is this?
-Just a moment, darling.
There's been a burglary.
Go in your room and see if you're missing anything.
Very kind, your stepson.
I don't exist
and that's fine for now.
Pierre, are you still there?
Thank you for coming so quickly.
I wanted to let Sara know immediately.
I have good news.
The juvenile court judge decided
that you can live with your father.
I don't know how to thank you.
-Thank the judge.
No, it's thanks to you.
Excuse me. I'm really sorry.
-Nothing wrong.
A familiar environment seemed to the judge
better after your mother's illness and death.
The rest is up to you, Mr. Evrard.
I hope that's clear.
-Certainly.
Youth care is watching.
Don't make me regret it.
Yes?
-Does this mean anything to you?
That's mine.
-I found him in the driveway...
...put it in my bag
and forgot to give it back to you.
No point.
My bag was stolen during the burglary.
How did that keychain come about?
in your pocket?
Are you going through my stuff now?
-Always, when I do the laundry.
I'm waiting for your explanation.
Don't know.
-Don't you be stupid.
Where are all the stolen items?
How so? Are you drunk?
-Burgling into your home. Nice mentality. Bravo.
But what your father thinks...
Do I tell him, or do you?
-You do it. I do not care.
I do not believe you.
You know me poorly.
May be, but downward spirals,
I know where it is difficult to get out.
Especially someone who is known to law enforcement.
Just call the cops
I do not care.
Why always those aggressive reactions?
Listen.
Let's go for the most intelligent
go option.
I can keep quiet about your father
and leave him out...
...but...
-But what?
But I want compensation.
-Which?
You're going to do your best
to integrate into this family.
Let's see if you can do that.
I see problem children every day, you know.
-I'm not a child.
Prove it.
What are you doing?
-I'm trying to get the beach stuff.
Wait a second.
Which one do you want?
-The swimming belts, the snorkels and...
Swimming belt.
-And the glasses.
Snorkel, goggles.
-Thank you.
Anything else?
-No, it's okay. That pink thing too.
Super.
-Was that it? That's five pounds.
I'm going swimming with the girls.
Would you like to come?
Why not.
We'll eat the salad first, girls.
-Yes, Mom, after that.
A pseudo-vegetarian.
A Big Mac is not meat.
It's too delicious.
Can't be resisted, that's all.
So you are no longer a vegetarian.
Great, I was tired of buying soy steaks.
I lasted two years.
It's cold.
Watch out, I'm going to splash you.
Look, little creatures.
-Theo. Theo, come. Theo, come back.
We don't dare go any deeper.
Can't get in?
-I do not feel.
Either you integrate into the family, or...
What are you doing, Theo?
Stop.
-Here.
That's mine.
Do not.
I've dumped guys
because they held me under water...
You can't dump me.
You don't hold back, you know.
-Never.
And tomorrow we go horse riding.
Are you coming too?
-Horse riding? I can't ride a horse.
When did you start?
When I was 12, with mom.
She loved it.
Do you miss Geneva?
Geneva sucks.
The people too. All money grubbers.
Invite who you want. You are at home.
I do not have friends.
Me neither.
How did you get that?
-I put that myself.
You realize you'll never be there again
comes from?
Do you realize that's bullshit?
You can have them removed straight away.
-Is that right?
You can remove them with white ink.
Or you can change them.
I can put one there, if you have the guts.
-Absolutely not.
Why not? Are you afraid?
-It's just not my thing.
You are afraid of pain. Everyone has them.
-Precisely.
Over there. I'll put one there. Really.
Or there. There yeah, come on.
That's chic. And I see you want it.
-Not at all.
You are afraid of pain. It just stings
a little. You'll love it.
Come on, just for fun. A little one there.
-No.
Yep, there. What you want.
Small, big, you can say so.
Over there.
-No.
Give me your arm.
Over there. I swear, here he comes.
Any other place is impossible.
If you put him there,
you will be chic for centuries.
That hurts.
-Don't show up.
Did you see mine?
Imagine that pain.
That's you.
I've never liked pain.
You really are a poser.
Because it's the first. It's addicting.
After this you'll be begging me for another one.
Then you say: Théo, get another tattoo.
-I'm sure not.
That is what you say now.
They all say that.
I'm trying.
Did Mona Lisa move constantly, do you think?
Good evening.
My stepmother Anne.
Amanda.
Good evening, madam.
It happened in Hamburg.
Hikers saw a huge lake near it
amounts of dead toads lying around.
Really a lot.
Which lake?
-I don't remember the name of the lake.
Don't ask those embarrassing questions.
-I know Hamburg a little.
Not me.
No, a massacre. Toad massacre.
About a thousand pieces. Voila.
And how did that happen?
-Exactly, that's a mystery.
Was the lake polluted? Toxic?
No, there were no dead toads
in the lake, but around it...
...and they had all exploded.
Was there an explosion in the water?
-Let him tell you.
I try to follow and understand it.
-Yes, he can ask questions.
And?
-In the first instance...
Boring shit?
-Giant.
I'm going to get butts. Are you coming?
-Why not.
Another?
Tell me, Amanda
hasn't been by in days.
It comes and it goes.
But is she still your girlfriend?
Girlfriend?
What are you talking about?
What should I say then?
-There's nothing to say.
She has her life, I have mine.
And what about your feelings?
Feelings aren't my thing.
Okay then. I did not say anything.
And you and my father?
What, me and your dad?
My father and you,
is that true love?
Do you really want me to tell you things?
about Pierre and me?
If I were my mother at your age
heard talk about men...
That made me feel sick.
Did she have many husbands, your mother?
-Fairly.
And you, before my father?
Everything is relative.
My mother was from the time of the pill
and the sexual revolution.
Everyone slept with everyone.
But not you?
-I am from the AIDS generation.
It came to an end immediately.
In one fell swoop.
Goodbye carelessness
and frivolity.
A window opened
and closed again.
But you've had plenty of men, right?
No comment.
I'm going.
-Amanda?
No comment.
Where were you? I called myself completely.
Have they left yet?
-Where were you?
I went for a walk.
We had visitors, you know.
-I felt like getting some air.
No.
You felt like making them feel
that you don't care about them.
Thank you on their behalf and on my behalf.
Is it too much to ask you, perhaps not
cordial, but behaving normally?
You know what I think of 'normopaths'?
They bore me to death.
And they bore themselves. Please be
not a normopath, it doesn't suit you.
Very sexy, and he says: You know about mine
special sexual relationship with women.
I say: Yes, I know.
To which he says:
I have an artistic project and...
Excuse me? An artistic project?
-Correct.
He takes his laptop
and show me pictures of him...
...making out with different women.
They are quite beautiful, but somewhat...
-That's quite a project.
Say that. And at some point
he says: I want you in this project, so...
Sorry to interrupt the outpourings.
With you I always feel like an intruder.
I would like to be a mouse
to know what you are saying.
Everything, down to the smallest detail.
Girls are coarser than men,
believe me.
Then I'd rather not know anything.
The children have been playing like crazy for an hour
on the trampoline. Worth a look.
Well, I'll tell you more...
-Yes, tell me.
Does not matter. Again.
Dad, come with us
play on the trampoline?
That's not possible, darling.
I have to pack my suitcase.
When I come back,
you are two days older.
Two days isn't much, right, honey?
Does your mobile phone never get any rest?
It's a great sci-fi series. Not the
usual junk. Brilliant. And French.
Would you like to see it?
That looks good.
I love it.
Théo, we must never do this again.
-Are you pinching him?
I'm not joking.
We must do
as if nothing happened and forget about it.
And above all, never do it again.
Promise me.
Wasn't it tasty?
-Yes. I let myself go.
But now we're in shit.
I shouldn't have done it, believe me.
Relax. It's not a drama.
Should I promise never to do it again?
Like a little naughty boy?
I'm not joking.
You're really annoying.
Locked up all day
in a gloomy convention center.
One seminar after another.
No time to enjoy the place.
Always the same.
I bought a new computer
for Theo.
Why?
-Then he's not constantly on his cell phone.
And he can work on it.
Couldn't you have discussed that?
Is it a problem
that I bought a computer for your son?
I might have him
want to give yourself.
Do I also have to ask permission?
if I cook for him or do his laundry?
In any case, it's sweet of you.
What's your favorite meal, Angela?
Just one?
-Yes.
Mom's spaghetti bolognese.
And if you could take one thing with you to
a desert island, what would that be?
Serena.
-But I'm not a thing, am I?
And what would you take with you?
to a desert island?
My duvet, my pillow
and my lightsaber to defend me.
Jokkebrok. You can't sleep
without your hug.
But if someone kills me,
what good is my cuddly toy?
Don't know.
Nothing.
-Nothing. That's true.
Do you want a beer?
But first the dictaphone.
Finally I will know everything about you.
You are very ambitious.
Do you swear to tell the truth?
-The truths.
Do not cheat.
Talk.
-Aren't you supposed to ask me questions?
Who are you?
You know that best.
What's best
that you have experienced?
Adopting the girls.
And the worst?
Then I realised
that I couldn't have children.
Your father and I have it
tried desperately.
Why didn't it work?
I had an abortion when I was very young.
That didn't go well. It fucked me up.
Who is your best friend?
-My sister.
Although she has always been very jealous of me.
And your biggest fear?
All that will disappear.
Or worse, that I did everything myself
to make everything disappear.
That's my fear of heights theory.
Fear of heights is not the fear of falling...
...but fear of the uncontrollable
temptation of the fall.
That one is so awful it's better
to jump so that fear stops.
You are really super complicated.
What is your favorite meal?
Roquefort.
That's not a meal.
-That depends on the quantity.
What are you taking with you?
to a desert island?
Matchsticks.
Smart.
Who did you sleep with first?
I don't want to talk about that.
You promised to answer all questions.
-I didn't promise anything.
Come on, tell me.
-I do not feel like it.
Why not?
There are things that never...
...never should have happened.
Like the two of us?
There is no two of us.
For me, yes.
-Quiet, that scares me.
Stop.
I can keep a secret,
but tell me about your first time.
Girls remember them all their lives.
-Stop.
I don't want and can't talk about it.
Too oppressive.
What is?
Sorry.
Am I making progress?
-Enormous.
You're so skinny.
I am small.
-Quiet.
Hello, Sara.
I wanted to know how you are.
With you.
It goes well.
I have often called
but you didn't answer.
I have another number.
I went to your school too...
...when I couldn't reach you.
-Sara.
They said you were sick.
Yes.
-What was wrong with you?
Sara, who are you talking to?
What did you think
from a walk?
Would you leave, please?
Why?
Child protection? I'm looking for the
handler of the Evrard file.
Sara Evrard.
Thank you.
I'll come and have a look.
-Come with me.
Stop.
I don't find that funny.
This is neither the time nor the place.
Hood with pus.
Hello. How beautiful they are.
-We're going to open the presents.
We're going to open our presents,
Lucas.
No, you're not allowed to touch it.
Only me.
Is it their birthday?
-Yes.
No, it's her birthday.
-Not his?
Her birthday.
Lucky.
Leave it alone.
Mom, will you fill my gun?
-Of course, honey.
So mean.
-Do not.
You're horny as hell.
Here?
You are completely...
You are completely reckless. No.
Come on, be cool.
A quickie, just for fun.
Stay. I'll explain.
-I'm not staying here a second longer.
What do I say to the girls?
-That you're doing it with their brother.
congratulations Serena
Congratulations
Mind you, it's still burning.
I haven't gotten Champomy yet.
Ask the Champoman.
Do you realize that we were yesterday
but narrowly escaped disaster?
You were super mean to me.
I just freaked out.
There is only one logical solution.
Which? Do not you want Me anymore?
-No.
We need our relationship
end immediately.
Are you that angry about yesterday?
-Incredibly dangerous.
Are you going to tell daddy everything?
-Are you crazy? That would be the worst.
This must remain secret
to keep up the appearance of a family.
Do you realize that?
Your father should never suspect anything.
Good.
-We won't tell him anything. To no one.
Promise?
Promise.
I hope I can trust you.
And from today everything stops.
So you're dumping me?
It had to end sometime.
You're young.
You so forgot.
And you?
That is different. You have your life
for you yet. You are free.
You will have dozens of girls,
live your life.
And if I don't feel like it?
You say that because you're young.
Kiss Me.
-It's over, I told you, right?
Are you denying me a kiss goodbye?
Kiss Me.
Okay, a kiss goodbye.
Then it's over.
Farewell.
Goodbye, my love.
You'll be jealous of my sexy
girlfriends. Then I don't need you anymore.
Mina called me.
What did she want?
-No idea. She didn't say anything.
I was thinking about a few days of one-on-one time
with Théo, in the chalet.
I took a week off.
I think he needs it
some time alone with me.
Go ahead.
If he still thinks afterwards
that you don't love him...
Is it a problem?
You never took time off
for the girls.
You think it's a bad idea.
No.
Do you want to come along?
I think he needs time with me.
Men among themselves.
You're probably right.
Come, let me adorn you,
like your sisters.
And she placed it on her head
a lily crown...
...of which every petal was a pearl.
Mom?
-Yes?
Why couldn't we come along too?
to the chalet?
Because daddy and Théo needed it
to go together.
What do you think they are doing?
What we do
when we go to the chalet.
Fishing, chopping wood, swimming,
make a fire in the garden, talk.
Mom, keep going.
-Excuse me.
There was a large three-master.
The little Mermaid
swam to the ship...
...and looked through the portholes
people in beautiful evening clothes.
The handsomest of them all was a prince...
Do you see the prince?
...who looked barely 16 years old.
Goodbye, my love. I just wanted to know
did you arrive safely...
...and whether you are having a good time.
The girls miss you.
Can you call me? Kiss.
What would you take with you?
to a desert island?
There are things that never
should never have happened.
Like the two of us?
Werewolves don't exist.
Yes.
-No.
Yes, they do exist.
-Have you ever seen one?
Bye, mom.
-Hello, Mom.
Day.
-Day.
Are Dad and Théo at home, do you think?
-Looks like it is.
Dad, daddy.
We came by taxi
from the riding school.
Mom broke the car.
-The gearbox.
I had to have it towed away.
Wouldn't you stay away for a week?
On your lap.
I cobbled something together.
Where is Theo?
-He's not eating with us.
Amanda.
-Amanda, indeed.
You always serve me first.
Did you notice that?
Do you know, girls,
when we arrived at the chalet...
...a mouse had gnawed through a pipe.
There was water everywhere.
We mopped it up, looked for the hole
and we found it behind the stove.
The stove had to be put aside. Happy
we could fix it with tape.
And the mouse?
-We sprinkled poison everywhere.
That's so mean.
-Yes, but you know...
Sit down and eat, darling.
Mice are cute, but they plant
move quickly and break a lot.
You can fix that.
-Yes, but you can't keep fixing things.
Don't you eat?
I'm not hungry.
Why aren't you hungry?
-Don't know.
Very good.
He bumps.
Sit down, we need to talk.
I spoke freely with Théo.
I said I was happy
with the chance of a life together.
How much I like the everyday things
had missed since he was little.
Suddenly he collapsed.
He said you guys...
That you had an affair with my son.
Don't you say anything?
That's despicable.
Insane.
You certainly didn't believe him, did you?
That miserable brat.
To come up with something so outrageous.
If you swallowed his lies,
you must have wanted that.
I just don't know.
I don't know what to believe.
Why would he say that?
if it wasn't true?
That seems clear to me.
To get attention.
That's all.
Why would I want an affair?
with your son?
He's a child.
-Stop.
He told me details.
Details he couldn't make up.
About how... How you...
We're not done yet.
-I do.
I swallowed so much of him.
I treated him with respect, care
and understanding, with this shit as thanks.
And you deny the mother
of your children, your wife...
...for the delirium of a disturbed child
that you barely know. I can't take this.
Stop. What are you doing?
He had a difficult life.
He taught me to hate because I so-called
took his father from his mother.
He wants to make us pay, but that is not the case
sorry for everything. And certainly not for you.
Calm down a bit.
-Do not touch me. Never again.
I only told
what my son said.
Dirty lies that you swallow.
-I don't know who to believe anymore.
Look at it from my side.
Imagine the hell I live in
since he said that.
Your son is a monster,
be aware of this.
Who do you think stole our stuff?
and broke into our house?
I didn't tell you anything. I liked that he
should be given a second chance.
For both of you.
I always take both of you into account.
You think you are so intelligent.
But you don't understand anything about others.
You don't understand anything.
Can't you see what game he's playing?
He wants you to reject me,
to have you all to themselves.
You are so easy to manipulate.
Even a child can do that.
I'm just asking you to explain...
-What? He won, period.
I know I don't have enough
been before you.
Not at all, in fact.
I'm sorry.
We have to talk
about what you said in the chalet.
What you accuse Anne of,
is serious.
No matter how angry we are, such a story
you are not allowed to invent. Do you understand?
Do not you believe me?
You don't lie about things like that.
I didn't lie.
Tell him.
-Apologize.
Don't worry about me, I'll be fine.
I understand that you are sad
and finds everything difficult.
But that...
Why did you do that?
You know that very well.
No not at all.
You're both crazy as hell.
We are a family.
We must be able to trust each other.
If not, you can't come here
continue to live.
You better give in
that you lied.
My patience is running out, Théo.
Speak.
Theo...
...it's not difficult.
Just say you lied.
If you say you lied,
I am willing to let it go.
Stay here.
I do not want you to leave.
Angela, Serena, the farewell is ready.
We have to go.
Cheer up, girls.
We will visit Théo at school.
Bye. Thank you.
-Bye.
Just ask if she can receive you.
Come on.
You have to tell Dad everything.
-I don't have to do anything.
You shouldn't have blurted it out.
Confessing is easy.
Soothe your conscience, so to speak. Take the
responsibility for your own shit.
And you don't have to?
-I have a family, you know.
Tell daddy I'm not lying. Otherwise...
-Otherwise?
Otherwise I will report it.
What exactly did I do to you?
do you think?
So that I understand.
You are an adult.
-And you're a child, then?
Did I abuse you?
Did I force you to have sex with me?
That's not the point.
-Why then?
You're twice as old as me.
You are my father's wife.
You really are scum.
I knew that, but that bad?
Fine.
Why would anyone believe you?
Because it's the truth.
-No way.
I haven't tried
to sleep with you. On the contrary.
I shouldn't have admitted, but that
it doesn't legally make it incest.
So what?
Why shouldn't it be my turn?
to lie?
Like I said, lowlife scum.
But fortunately it is not that simple.
It's your word against mine
and I will sell my skin dearly.
You have no proof.
A pending criminal case,
a motive for revenge.
Besides, you're taking revenge on me.
No.
-No one will listen to you.
You are not credible.
Much easier to say your father
that you made it all up...
...instead of being stubborn.
You're young. You will enjoy much more
have to swallow in your life.
You better leave this alone, you know?
I am not your enemy.
Hello, Sara.
-I was allowed to come and give this to you.
How do I get flowers?
-I just wanted to thank you...
...for everything you've done for me.
You helped me.
How is your father?
-I have a host family until he gets better.
They're quite nice.
-That's nice.
Can I call you...
...to tell you how things are going?
-Please.
Merry Christmas, Sara.
-Merry Christmas.
Who was that?
-That was Sara. A client.
Did she give you a bouquet of flowers?
-Yes. Nice huh?
I'm going to put them in a vase.
I'm so glad you came.
That's so important to me. Thank you.
You're my sister after all.
You know very well
that I can't stay mad at you for long.
Look at that.
Look. There is a snowman
on top of. Look.
Is it too little cake?
-No, it's a little too much cocoa butter.
I prefer chestnut cream.
Santa Claus has visited.
That's impossible?
Yes, Santa Claus has been there.
It's a dog. A small dog.
-What a sweetheart.
Is this for me?
-Yes.
That's for you.
-I don't get anything?
What is that? Why don't I get that?
-Exactly what I wanted.
What is it?
-I wonder where my...
I don't know if this is for Angela,
or for Serena, or...
Maybe it's for Anne.
-For me maybe?
What does it say? Guard...
What does it say? Ah, for me.
-It says Anne.
Yes.
-Yes, young lady.
Wait a second.
Maybe you don't like it.
He spoiled you well.
-You are out of your mind.
He's gorgeous.
Mr. Farad can see you.
Dear colleague, per mandate
I will file a criminal case against you...
...under 222-22-3 for serious
facts for which my client is suing you.
I would like to know what your position is
and whether you want to settle.
I want to say that, given the situation
which I, forgive me my dear colleague...
...know a little better than you, without completely
misrepresentation of the truth...
...there is no reason
to quote article 222-22-3.
I want my stepson to know
that I find this blackmail abject.
We don't ask you about your feelings.
Your client is a liar.
His accusations
make no sense...
...and he knows it.
-Don't address him directly.
Please indicate if you would like
whether we continue this or not.
If not, I will present the matter
at the Public Prosecution Service and the bar.
I accept your proposal.
That's for the best.
I won't waste your time anymore.
Send our agreement
to my office.
Of course.
Goodbye, Theo.
What the hell are you doing?
See you.
Why?
-To see you.
We had a deal, right?
There's no fucking deal.
I have accepted everything.
It cost me a fortune.
What else do you want? Torment me?
Then see how you are doing.
You are drunk.
You don't know what you're doing anymore.
Be reasonable.
Stop.
Say you're not in love with me.
You're crazy. Completely crazy.
You're crazy too.
Crazy about me.
What was it?
That was Theo.
He was drunk.
I called a taxi.
You're freezing.
Pierre...
-Quiet.