NETFLIX PRESENTS
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
[WARDEN IN SPANISH]
ID card, please. Thanks.
-Hi. ID card, please.
-[VISITOR] Mr. Warden…
[WARDEN] Can I see your ID?
[GUARD IN ENGLISH]
Your attention, please! Olga Agüil López.
Vanessa Ropero Rodríguez.
Paqui Molina López.
Ready for your visit.
IGNACIO CAÑAS
25B 3º 2º MAIGNON ST, 08012 BARCELONA
[PENSIVE GUITAR MUSIC PLAYING]
HI, GAFITAS. IT'S BEEN A WHILE, HASN'T IT?
I HOPE YOU REMEMBER ME.
EL ZARCO AND I TALK ABOUT YOU A LOT.
[WOMAN] Come on, spit it.
-[CHILD COUGHING]
-Spit the candy. Come on.
Spit it out. Come on. Spit it out.
[CONTINUES COUGHING]
Spit the candy.
[MUFFLED GASPING]
-[CHILD COUGHING]
-Come on, give it to me.
[CHILD GASPING FOR BREATH]
Okay, okay. All right, now.
It's okay. It's over. It's over.
Okay. All good now.
[MAN] Come on, kid. Breathe!
Come on, kid. Breathe, breathe!
Jeez, you scared me.
What happened?
Nothing.
I think I got dizzy.
You all right?
Yeah, yeah. I'm fine.
Come on. Get up.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
[BOY 1] Hey!
[BOY 2] Hey, Nachito!
-[LAUGHTER]
-[BOY 3] Bye, Nacho.
[BOY 2] Look at him.
He's so scared. Where you going, man?
[GIRL] You're always picking on him.
Leave him alone.
-[LAUGHTER]
-What did he ever do to you?
-[BOY 3] What a loser.
-[CAT MEOWS]
[BELL TOLLING]
OUTLAWS
[MAN ON TV] the Spanish Constitution.
But everyone locks their
bikes near the pool's entrance.
Someone must've seen something.
It must've been a kid.
He probably had a bike just like yours.
-Well, I asked. Nobody saw anything.
-I think you're making this up.
-[WOMAN] Cristina!
-What?
Since he got his grades, all we ever
hear him say is, "I want a motorbike."
[MAN] There'll be no motorbike
and no wheels for the bike.
Our vacation's coming up
and we'll need the money.
-For the moment, just walk.
-Yes, but you have to watch yourself.
If you don't pay attention,
they'll steal your purse.
One of the girls at work
got mugged the other day.
Right in the middle of the city.
Poor girl is still rattled.
[WOMAN SIGHS] What is the world coming to?
Here, honey.
[IN SPANISH]
A new era in Spanish history begins today.
-[NACHO IN ENGLISH] Dad.
-What?
-I need money.
-Again?
-You just got your allowance.
-There's a new film coming out tomorrow.
I wanna go with some friends,
but I'm flat broke.
Yeah, all right.
But that's it until next week, huh?
-There isn't much left.
-Thanks.
[ACTOR IN SPANISH] Come in.
Take it easy.
EMMANUELLE COMING SOON
I told you. I don't like coming here.
Come on.
TODAY WATCH OUT, WE'RE MAD
-One, please.
-It's already started.
It's okay.
[IN SPANISH] He didn't do it on purpose.
I did it on purpose.
[GRUNTS]
[UPBEAT, WHIMSICAL MUSIC PLAYING]
Hey, man, how you doing?
Haven't seen you all day.
-You been hiding or what?
-Didn't go swimming, Nacho?
No need to. He's still wet.
-No, man. That's sweat.
-Give them back.
-Or what?
-Or he's gonna get angry.
Nah. Nachito doesn't get mad, right?
He appreciates a good joke.
You like a good laugh.
That's why you're watching this.
You saw that? That was synced.
Oh, man. Oh, my God. Look, look, look.
Why are you picking on me?
We used to be friends, Víctor.
-What? You guys were friends?
-No.
-Last year.
-That was before you came.
-Seriously?
-[VÍCTOR] Of course not.
-What?
-See? He doesn't get angry.
But you, man, you always get so defensive.
-Hey!
-Wait!
-You're not leaving already?
-Not so fast, buddy.
The movie isn't over yet, Nacho.
Look. Look.
[OVERLAPPING GRUNTS, LAUGHTER]
Stop it right now.
What the hell are you doing?
-Nothing. We're just helping.
-[USHER] Get out.
-All of you, out. Out!
-All right, all right.
-[USHER] Get out.
-Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, well,
at least give us our money back.
-Hey, he's running! Come back.
-No, no, let him go. It's okay.
Let him go.
[CRYING]
[FRUSTRATED GROANING]
[TV] Unless you buy bonds…
-Nacho.
-…From the Bank of Catalonia…
-Hey.
-They yield 12% and…
Where have you been?
We've already finished dinner.
Doesn't matter. I'm not hungry.
…you get a 26,000-peseta tax cut.
How much is the tax cut
for 100,000 pesetas?
26,000.
[DOOR SLAMS]
What's wrong with him?
Told you. He's been acting strange.
Cash bonds at 12%
from the Industrial Bank of Catalonia.
Visit any of our branches
for more details.
Don't delay, they're in high demand.
[ROCK MUSIC PLAYING]
[CRISTINA KNOCKING ON DOOR] Nacho.
Nacho, open up.
Just leave me alone.
Yeah, well, at least turn down the music.
Dad's gonna get mad.
You hear me?
Come on, you looking for a fight?
[MUSIC STOPS]
Well, you don't have to turn it off.
You're playing the martyr now.
[NACHO SIGHS]
Aren't you gonna say something?
Oh, come on, Nacho.
I'm trying to help you here.
All right, then go to hell.
[PINBALL MACHINE BEEPING, CHIMING]
Excuse me, can I get a bag of chips?
[INTENSE SYNTH MUSIC PLAYING]
Hey, where do you think you're going?
What's wrong, chief?
We're here to play a few games.
I don't want any problems.
You cause trouble, I'm throwing you out.
-Is that clear?
-Yes, sir.
[MAN] Can I get some change?
[PLAYER] Ah, yes!
[PLAYER] No way, man.
Fucking Invaders. I'm already dead.
How is he?
He's not bad.
Pretty obvious.
You've played this before, huh, Gafitas?
Glasses boy.
Let's go find another one.
He'll be here all day.
No, I want this one.
[SIGHS] Tere made up her mind.
Looks like we'll be watching
Buck Rogers here till the sun goes down.
Do you want to...
You hear that? Gentleman.
Great.
Come here a lot, don't you?
Yeah. Once in a while.
Does it ever get busy?
It's kinda dead now.
Well, it's early.
But it'll be packed later.
That guy's pretty smart.
I'm sure he's raking in a fortune
doing fuck-all all day.
Tere.
You go on.
Do you know these hooligans?
-No, I don't.
-What were you talking about?
Nothing. She wanted to play,
but I was here.
I don't like it
when people like that start coming here.
They always seem to bring trouble.
What are you doing now?
What, me? Going home.
I have no money left.
Move.
[PINBALL MACHINE BEEPING RAPIDLY]
[NACHO CHUCKLES]
-You gotta help me close up later, though.
-Yeah, for sure.
Go on, play.
[CHUCKLES]
VILARÓ ARCADE
[WOMAN IN CATALAN]
to Anton's house. I've got a lettuce.
Tomorrow, can I count on you?
Yes, yes.
All right. See you tomorrow.
[WOMAN ON TV] What's next
for Ira von Fürstenberg? Any films?
Yeah, I was shooting
in Brazil and Paraguay.
Now I'm gonna write two books.
One's about women around the world.
It's interesting.
And, well, I'm
routine as well, of course…
Nacho, you're pushing it, you know?
You realize how late it is?
Is there any mayo?
If you're gonna come home late,
you could at least call.
-We wouldn't worry then.
-I had no coins left.
Here's the mayo.
Got myself a job.
-A job doing what?
-At the arcade. I help him close up.
Huh? That's a job?
-I get 10 free games every day.
-They should pay you something.
I get 10 games,
but I have to wait till they close.
-That's why I'm late.
-God almighty.
Really, Nacho? You're a complete idiot.
[SCOFFS]
[MAN ON TV] Devor-Olor insoles…
Ira, name one bad thing
about the class you belong to.
Least he's not spending money.
It's better than nothing.
[SCOFFS] I don't know.
Don't know what to say, truly.
Working at an arcade.
The beliefs of that world…
This thing isn't working.
Hang on.
-What's wrong?
-It's the foosball table over there.
They put in a coin,
but the ball didn't come out.
Ah, who knows what they put in it?
Here. You deal with it.
How you doing, chief?
It's not real.
That's not my problem.
I put in a real coin.
Now look at you, big honcho.
Barely a month,
and he's got the fat man's job.
Yes, sir. That's very good.
You're climbing up the ladder.
[TERE] Ah, to the right.
No, not there. No. No.
Zarco, this is not how it goes.
You don't move, you just stay put.
-[TERE] You don't know how to play.
-[ZARCO] Bullshit.
[TERE] Hit it, hit it!
Hey, man. I need change.
I don't have any. Go to the booth.
-You're dead. Yup. You're dead.
-Shit. I keep losing.
Zarco.
So what now? You coming?
You're such an asshole. I'm staying.
Yeah.
Ask me to play.
Come on. You play one, and then I play.
Okay?
Who was that guy?
Who?
The guy on the stairs.
A pusher. Getting some chocolate.
You know what that is, right?
Of course I know what it is.
But you've never smoked.
Shit. You play.
If you want to try it, come to La Font.
It's a bar in Chinatown.
-In Chinatown?
-Yeah.
We smoke out on the square
every afternoon. It's always cool.
If you wanna come, you're invited.
[SIGHS] Your turn.
Well, coming or what?
Yeah, maybe.
Gafitas, I'm hot, right?
Come with me.
[ARCADE PATRONS CHATTERING]
Much better like this.
-What are you doing?
-What do you think?
I'll stop if you want.
But you don't want, I can tell.
Uh, what if that girl
goes and tells Mr. Tomàs?
We'll have to be quick, then.
[NACHO BREATHING HEAVILY]
[KNOCKING AT DOOR]
Don't stop.
[TERE CHUCKLES]
[NACHO BREATHING RAPIDLY]
[NACHO GRUNTS]
Are you done?
All right, then.
See you tomorrow at La Font.
[NACHO] Oh!
[SIGHS]
[UP-TEMPO GUITAR MUSIC PLAYING]
Hey there, beautiful.
You're so handsome.
[WOMAN] See ya!
-Hey, Pepe, how you doing?
-[PEPE] Hey.
How are you, big man?
-You girls heard what happened?
-What?
-An explosion. A train canister.
-Come on.
-Come with me.
-Well, hello.
Look at you, poor boy. All alone.
Come to Mama, darling.
Where are you going, sweetheart?
Lovely boy.
What a handsome young man.
-[OVERLAPPING CHATTER]
-[FAST-PACED GUITAR MUSIC PLAYING]
Hey, you.
Come here a sec.
Come. I'm not gonna hurt you.
Come here.
-Gimme a smoke.
-I don't smoke.
-You don't smoke?
-Don't be a dick.
-Just asking for a cigarette.
-No. I don't smoke. I don't have any.
Yeah, sure. Want me to search you?
You're just a dumb-ass.
Chino, back off.
He's a friend of mine. Okay?
Dickhead's your friend?
Don't mind Chino.
He just likes people to give him stuff.
Look, Tere. We've got a visitor.
Hi, Gafitas.
Well, let's go have a drink.
I'll introduce you to the gang.
Did you guys hear about the pope?
-I don't give a shit about the pope.
-Yeah, man, but this is huge.
They killed him.
He's been there, what, a month?
-How should I know?
-That shit has got to stop.
He just doesn't get it.
I'm gonna have to make things
very clear to him.
No more pussy-footing.
Lay down the law. [MEN LAUGHING]
Maybe that's why they killed him.
He wouldn't let them stick it up his ass.
Well, my mother's all upset.
Now what? What are they gonna do?
What do you mean?
They lock themselves up
and pick another one.
They gotta smoke enough doobies
to get their white smoke.
What else?
Well, then check this out.
They should pick me.
Pure white smoke!
[MEN LAUGHING]
Really?
[LAUGHS] There you go.
-What's up, Guille?
-Not much.
Oh, you look rough, man.
I just had a snooze. Feel like a new man.
-[MAN] Lucky you.
-Who's that?
-[ZARCO] That's Gafitas.
-From the arcade, right?
My name's Nacho.
Go on. Tell them
you're that fatso's right-hand man.
Uh, well, I help him out
every now and then.
Every now and then?
You're not there every day?
Yes, I help him close up.
[ZARCO] Sure.
The guy's so fat,
he can't move his own money bags.
He must take in a good amount.
No idea.
I don't deal with the money. I don't know.
But you go to the bank with him.
Right?
No, he... he goes alone on his moped.
You gonna smoke or look at it?
Come on. Take a hit.
-Yeah, come on, man. Don't be afraid.
-Come on.
[DOG BARKING]
[COUGHING]
[ALL LAUGH]
-Give it here.
-Check him out. He's turning yellow.
[OVERLAPPING CHATTER]
-All right, cheers everybody.
-[GLASSES CLINKING]
[MAN] Cheers. [CHUCKLING]
You're white as a ghost, man.
You smoked quite a bit.
-You might throw up.
-I'm fine.
-It's just that...
-What?
Are you guys
planning on robbing the arcade?
Why do you say that?
Well, they've been asking me questions.
Who asked you what?
The guy in the dark blue shirt.
-That's Guille.
-Yeah, and the other guys, too.
Nah, they're just nosy.
Always wanna know everything.
Yeah.
Do you think I'm lying?
Huh?
You think that's why I invited you?
Are you fucking serious?
-I think I'm gonna go.
-Go, then.
Run back home.
No. I'm just stepping outside.
I'm feeling sick.
Should I go with you?
No, I'm good. I'll go.
[DOOR OPENS]
First time, I chucked last year's lunch.
Don't worry. You'll get used to it.
I'm feeling better.
What's that Tere told me?
I dunno what she told you.
Guille's a bit of an asshole.
I dunno why he's asked you all that.
Anyway, what do you care
if we wanna steal
from the guy at the arcade?
I want nothing to do with it, okay?
Of course not.
You don't need to know. It's our thing.
-I don't want it to be 'cause of me.
-Gafitas, you told us he drives a moped.
You didn't give us
the combination to the safe.
I don't wanna hurt the guy.
Why? Is he your friend?
I like him. He's a good man.
You like him.
All right. That's a whole other thing.
If you don't want anything
to happen to him, it won't.
You serious?
From now on, the fat guy is sacred.
But let me tell you something.
You owe me one, Gafitas.
[REPORTER] A Vatican diplomat
who was not used to
the inner workings of the papal curia.
John Paul I. No one would have bet on him.
Since this morning,
preparations are underway
at the Sistine Chapel,
where the conclave will meet
and choose a new pope.
The chimney from which
the white smoke will rise…
[SCOFFS]
Come on, Nacho. This isn't funny.
-Oh, boy. He's got a problem.
-Shut up.
-What's with you two?
-Just look at his face.
Look at your own face.
Be nice to your sister.
She should be nice to me.
I didn't say anything.
You really don't look well, my boy.
You sure you're okay?
Mom, he's never felt better.
Can't you see? He's high as a kite.
-What? Did you smoke?
-Get off my back.
[FATHER] Watch your tone.
You're talking to your mother.
-Where are you going?
-My room.
No. Sit down and eat your food.
I'd say you smoked at least two joints.
Nacho! And you too, you be quiet.
What's all this about joints?
Have you been smoking drugs?
Hmm?
That's what you do now?
You smoke and drink?
Is that why you're acting up?
Just go to hell.
What? Say that again.
Nacho, come back here. I'm talking to you.
Come back here right now. Nacho!
When did you start smoking?
You were 14, 15?
Well, I'm 17, Dad.
You ever talk to me like that again,
I'll give you a good smacking.
[DOOR OPENS, CLOSES]
-See you tomorrow.
-Good night.
That guy looks like a watermelon
on his tiny red moped.
Strong moped.
You missed it today.
Guille was such a pain. He kept insisting
he wanted to do it no matter what.
But Zarco stopped him.
If it hadn't been for him,
fat guy would've had a bad time.
And so would you.
And of course, uh, you knew nothing?
No, I knew, but I didn't know
it mattered so much to you.
Well, yeah. It matters to me.
That's why I'm here,
to tell you not to worry.
Nothing will happen.
What, don't wanna hang with us anymore?
Don't know.
Well, it's too bad.
They all like you a lot.
And, uh... and you?
Would you be upset if I was gone?
What do you think?
All right, Gafitas.
See you. Take care.
Tere.
What?
I'll see you tomorrow.
Cool.
[ENERGETIC ROCK MUSIC PLAYING]
[TERE] Come on. You're not even trying.
Shut up. I have a game plan.
[MAN SPEAKS INDISTINCTLY]
-Piernas, I'm kicking your ass, man.
-Get lost.
Hey, look who's here.
Got rid of the specs.
Wow, look at those puppy eyes.
-Well, hello, good-looking.
-You moron!
Aw, man, just my fucking luck. Shit.
-It's not luck. You suck.
-Go fuck yourself, man.
It's just... I can't think
when I'm playing against Madrid.
-Tere, you and the kid?
-Why not?
[CHINO] Plus I'm playing with you.
Guille, come here.
I don't wanna play with this loser.
-No one wants to play with you, Chino.
-Come on. You're playing with me.
-We'll kick their asses. Let's go.
-Come on.
Hurry up, kick the ball.
-Quick and easy.
-Shut up. Drop the ball in.
[CHINO] Show us what you got.
Come on.
[TERE] Fuck!
-Ooh!
-[LAUGHTER]
Okay, so who's the loser now?
Shut up, and don't drink my beer.
Come on, play.
[ZARCO] Come on. Shit. Do it.
That's it.
Whoo!
Come on, snap out of it.
I wanna see them squirm.
Can't score, can you?
Shit. Look at this kid.
He doesn't even need his glasses.
Bet you can speak Catalan too.
Of course I speak Catalan.
I don't. Not a fucking word.
Guille here, even less.
Go, go, go, go!
-Amazing!
-That's how you launch a comeback.
That's how it's done.
Next time, I'm playing with you.
I was thinking we should take him with us.
Who? This kid?
[ZARCO] Yeah.
I'm sure he'll come in handy.
-Tere, what do you say?
-I'm into it, but he won't want to.
Well, we're gonna have to ask him.
But…
You owe me one.
-[IN CATALAN] Hello.
-Hi.
-Is Pau home?
-Pau? There's no Pau here.
I thought she lived here. My mistake.
-How old is Pau?
-Our age.
Then she won't be next door either.
Their kids are older.
Sorry for bothering you.
-[TERE] Thank you.
-Bye.
Okay?
Yeah. For God's sake,
don't squeeze so hard.
You'll break my hand.
-Sorry.
-No, it was good.
I'm sure that woman is
watching us from the door.
There, you see? Wasn't that hard.
Anyway, we make a nice couple, don't we?
[CHUCKLES]
-Let's do that one.
-All right.
[TINNY POP MUSIC PLAYING OVER CAR STEREO]
Hey.
[TERE] Piece of cake.
It's on a corner. Easy to enter.
You sure no one's home?
Yeah. The neighbors are gone too.
Come on, Gordo. Move your ass.
[JAUNTY SPANISH POP SONG PLAYS]
Come on, get closer.
[NACHO SIGHS]
Like this?
Come on, a bit more. I won't bite.
Your hands on my ass.
Stop looking around and focus on me.
That's good.
You're getting the hang of it.
What if someone comes?
If someone comes,
just stick your tongue down my throat.
They'll cross the street for sure.
Oh, Gafitas.
Strange time to get a boner.
What the fuck? Come on!
Yeah, yeah. Chill.
They're taking too long.
You in a rush?
Oh, watch out!
Oh, false alarm.
[GUILLE] Open the trunk!
Go.
♪ I'm from the island
The island of Japan ♪
♪ I smoked four joints
That my girlfriend offered me… ♪
Check this out, Tere.
Gordo found that under the panties.
[GORDO] What?
What is it? Gold?
This is real gold.
-What you doing?
-What does it look like?
-It's a man's.
-But I like it.
-It says F.M.
-Exactly. "For Me."
-[TERE CHEERS]
-Come on, man, show us how it's done!
[DISCO MUSIC PLAYING]
[TERE] Looking good!
The night is yours, man!
You seen Piernas?
That guy can sure dance. He's amazing.
-Here, take this.
-I already got one.
Nah, that's just ice by now. Take it.
Fucking great, isn't it? Fucking great!
Piernas, you're my hero!
Yeah, right. Here we go.
Get a room, fathead!
Mind your own fucking business.
I've got the yellow ones.
Talidons? That's for grannies.
Give me something good.
These pink ones are for pussy.
Make your engine throb.
What are you talking about?
I don't want that.
Rohypnol, you got any of those?
I do, but that's another kettle of fish.
We're talking about serious money.
Don't worry about money.
I've got money, see?
Come on, now. Get real, all right?
That'll do.
What have you got, Merche?
-Show me the goods.
-Yeah, yeah.
Careful what you take.
You might be smart,
but you might end up brain-dead.
-Sure thing. Thanks, beautiful.
-Get out of here.
Hey, look at those two.
Which two?
Those girls.
The redhead and the brunette.
-Let's go talk to them.
-Nah, fuck it.
-Why not?
-Because I don't feel like it.
Yeah, but I do.
You take the redhead. Chat with her.
I'm going after the brunette.
-Drácula, for you.
-Hey, cool. Thanks.
And, ah, here's one for you too.
And what is it?
With this, you'll have
the time of your fucking life.
Ooh, don't just stare at it.
It's just medicine. Ain't gonna hurt ya.
[DISCO MUSIC STOPS,
ROMANTIC POP MUSIC PLAYS]
You coming?
Hey, you coming or what?
Ah, go to hell.
Stop staring at her.
You'll strain your eyes.
Who's the guy she's with?
That guy? No idea.
Never seen him before.
Isn't she Zarco's girlfriend?
[LAUGHS]
You'd better ask her about that, okay?
[MOTHER] Nacho, come on, get up.
Two o'clock in the afternoon.
You gave us quite a fright last night.
[GRUNTS] What happened, Mom?
Your sister found you on the landing.
Your father is furious.
Come on, get up.
And clean yourself up.
The table's already set.
God almighty, this stinks.
Don't know if I should wash it
or throw it away.
Don't touch it. Leave it.
You wash it yourself, okay?
[REPORTER] The sun will shine
in most of Spain,
with passing clouds in some areas.
The unsettled weather in the southeast
continues but is expected to ease.
Light cloudy intervals will affect…
[CROWD CHATTERING, LAUGHING]
Do it. Let's do it.
-Yeah, absolutely.
-We need money, man.
I'm talking about Gerona.
-The one in the square.
-That one.
Who here's gonna get us a car?
El Zarco,
you know I'm the best with wires.
Done deal. We'll do what we always do.
Nacho!
-Hey, man! What's up?
-Hey, how's your head today?
It's better now.
But this morning... Oh, man.
Yesterday, you jumped into the speakers.
No shit. I don't remember.
Man, you were so high,
you almost got kicked out of the disco.
Yeah, and then when
he jumped on that guy...
If Zarco hadn't been there,
you'd be dead meat by now.
Isn't that what friends are for?
All right, so we're good?
It's tomorrow, right?
Fine with me, but it's up to them.
-I'm in.
-Nah, I'll pass.
You're a chicken.
Especially when you've got cash.
It doesn't matter.
Us with Tere. We're fine.
-[ZARCO] Tere isn't coming.
-Where's Tere?
Around, but we can't count on her.
Forget about it then.
What about Lina?
Mmm, no. Don't mix my girl in this.
She gets really nervous. She can't do it.
What do you guys need?
GERONA BANK
TELEPHONE
-Hey, how are you doing?
-I'm good.
-[MAN] How are you?
-Good. I think it's gonna work out.
Just need confirmation.
-[MAN] For sure, then?
-Yes. Yeah.
[ENGINE IDLING]
[BELL TOLLING]
-Excuse me. Excuse me.
-Huh? Yes.
-I'm looking for this street.
-Yes?
-Is it near here?
-Yes.
Uh, it's just here, on the right.
-Which one? I was just there.
-[MAN] Over there.
Not the first one.
-You mean there?
-The second to the right.
[MAN] Hey! Hey! Hey!
[ENGINE REVVING]
-Hey!
-Fuck, man, I dropped it.
Shit!
[PASSERSBY CLAMORING]
[PASSERBY] Can you hear me?
No, don't move him.
-Call a doctor.
-Sir?
[EXHILARATED LAUGHTER]
[UP-TEMPO DISCO MUSIC PLAYS]
Shit, man, look at the cash the guy had.
He even had American money.
-[DRÁCULA] We're gonna have a good time.
-Yes, sir.
[EXCITED CHATTER]
You're good, my boy.
Oh, man, I need a drink.
Hey! Oh, cool.
-All right.
-Good evening, ladies and gentlemen.
-Evening.
-[GORDO] Liven up the place.
A rum and Coke for me.
Go on, have something to drink.
Marta, give us
a couple of beers, all right?
Same old for me, lady.
-Hey.
-Hey there, beautiful.
-How you doing?
-Colette, how you doing?
Take it easy, Zarco.
Don't go crazy. I know you too well.
Come on. Relax.
Gafitas, come over here.
You're gonna have so much fun.
This is what you do after you score big.
Evening. You're looking good.
[ZARCO] Gafitas.
Come over here.
I wanna introduce you to a friend.
Right on.
-Hello, handsome. What's your name?
-Nacho.
I'm Francesca.
AKA Paqui.
This is the young man
I was telling you about.
You're very handsome, you know.
Tell her something nice.
See how hot she is?
Zarco.
-You touch it, you pay for it.
-This is the good thing about this place.
Things are clear. See?
I give this lady 5,000 pesetas,
and then you go with her
and have the time of your life.
Who? Me?
-Yes, you.
-No, no, no, no.
-Yes, yes. Come on, man. Go.
-No.
You've earned it.
[CHINO] Oh, shit.
Hey, Zarco.
Give me some. Come on, man.
Buy me a whore, Zarco.
Chino, you're a whore.
[WATER RUNNING]
Do you want me to wash your dick?
Uh, no. I'm... I'm good, thanks.
Don't worry. We have plenty of time.
-It's just that I...
-Yeah, yeah, I know.
What do you know?
Well, I know that, uh...
Just what Zarco told me.
That you're still a little shy, maybe.
But it's okay, you know. Just come closer.
Is something wrong?
-I don't know.
-What's wrong? You don't like me?
-No, no, no.
-You don't like my tits?
No, no. Yes.
Did you know in the US,
they put stuff in them
to make them bigger?
-Really?
-Yes.
I've always wanted to have massive tits,
but people tell me they find them nice.
Yes. Yes.
You like them?
Yes, they're... they're beautiful.
You like this?
Is that better?
You can lick them if you want.
I think I... I'd better go.
No, come on. You can't go.
-Yes.
-No, wait, I understand.
It's your first time.
It's scary at the beginning.
-You're nervous. It's very normal.
-Don't worry. Really.
You're beautiful.
But, here.
But, no, really…
Don't tell anyone, all right?
No, no, don't worry.
Oh, shit.
-What?
-You can't leave now. Can't go down.
See that light? Means the police are here.
[COLETTE] Ooh, looking good tonight.
Nothing compared to you.
How you doing, babe?
I'm bored out of my skull.
Yeah. It's kinda dead tonight, isn't it?
And who's this cutie?
Assistant Inspector Cuenca.
And this here is Colette,
Gerona's most exciting woman.
If you say so.
Pleasure.
-So you're new around here?
-Isn't it obvious?
-Guy just got here.
-It's his first assignment,
so we thought,
"Let's take him to La Vedette
so he can lose his virginity."
Well, I'm sure you already know
it's not a problem here.
-No, no, no.
-What do you mean?
-Another day.
-Another day, he says.
Well, what can I get you?
Rum and Coke for you?
-A short one.
-Short one, right?
Short on Cola.
-[LAUGHS] She knows me too well.
-Alfonso, whiskey?
-Yeah, whiskey.
-And what can I get you?
-Also whiskey.
-Hmm?
Yeah, but give him the good stuff, huh?
-Poor guy just got here.
-[LAUGHS]
What a bunch of dirty bastards.
[PAQUI] The worst one is the boss.
He's a slimeball.
One time, I had to go with him,
and it was fucking gross.
And in exchange, he leaves you alone?
Hmm. My lady-boss,
they eat out of her hand.
And on weekends, when we're busiest,
they don't even come near.
We're gonna be here awhile, then.
[PAQUI] Yes.
I'm glad we're together. I'm good.
I'm just here to relax.
No, no, I'm good. Thanks.
This is what's good about small places.
See, any sucker
who wants to move stolen goods
or needs people for some job or other
has to pass this neighborhood.
So you don't have a choice.
You gotta know this neighborhood
like the back of your hand.
The most dangerous thing
you're gonna find here
is cirrhosis or gonorrhea. [LAUGHS]
Close your eyes.
-What are you gonna do?
-Nothing, trust me. Just close your eyes.
Okay, now I want you
to think about a girl you really like.
I'm sure there is one.
Because you don't have
a girlfriend, do you?
No, not yet.
Well, it doesn't matter.
There's probably
a girl at school or a neighbor.
Yes. There's a girl.
Well, just imagine her.
Are you seeing her?
Yeah.
And what is she doing?
She's dancing.
And looks at you.
She smiles at you.
You get close to her.
Even closer.
Closer.
So close you're almost touching.
Then suddenly, she leans in…
[SULTRY POP SONG PLAYS]
Give it here.
What's wrong? Don't like to dance?
I can't dance.
You can't roll a joint either,
but you still smoke them.
I've been told of a few things you can do.
Who told you what?
You fishing for compliments?
You already know.
-You scored big-time, didn't you?
-The guy was loaded.
Who would've thought?
That boyish face of yours.
But I'm not a kid.
No, I know that too.
You're a man now, right, Gafitas?
Too bad.
What?
I would've liked
your first time to be with me,
instead of with a whore.
Who told you?
-Chino.
-Fucking Chino.
Lina is pissed off.
Gordo won't be fucking for a while.
And Zarco?
Zarco should know.
-You're angry too.
-No, I'm not angry.
But I don't like it.
I don't like whores.
Tere, you do what you want.
It's different.
The other day, you fucked mustache guy.
Yeah. So?
It's one thing to fuck whoever you want,
and another to get fucked
by someone you give money to.
Zarco, gimme something.
Don't have anything.
I'm broke. You have any money?
The old hag doesn't trust me.
She won't give me any credit.
The bitch is stingy as fucking hell.
With all the money she's been taking
from me for those fucking pills,
no way she's gonna spoil my fun.
Guille, we're leaving. Where's Tere?
She's outside.
Very well. You wanted some?
You're coming too.
[MAN] There you go.
[ZARCO] Guille, take your jacket off.
-Come on, man.
-I told you, take it off.
Have a nice night.
-Good evening.
-I'd like some suppositories.
-Glycerin?
[NACHO] Yes, please.
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
Hush. Don't blow it.
Here you are. Forty-five pesetas.
Thank you.
[GASPS]
[NACHO] Are you all right?
Hey, hey, what's wrong?
Breathe.
-Breathe.
-[GROANING] I can't.
I think she's having her baby.
No, I can't.
You'll be all right.
-Breathe deeply. It's gonna be okay.
-I can't.
I'll call an ambulance.
-Come on. Let's go in. Don't try me.
-[PHARMACIST] Okay.
He's so cute. He looks like you.
[CONFIDENT ROCK MUSIC PLAYS]
Quick, somebody help!
You gotta breathe. Breathe.
[NACHO] That's it. Breathe]
[OFFICER] Basically, they took
prolintane, Centramine, rohypnol,
Valium, Bustaids…
Well, they knew
exactly what they were after.
Yes. They also took everything
in the register and 5,000 pesetas.
And the car was right there.
They got in,
and a minute later they were gone.
-Two plus a driver. Can you describe them?
-Yes.
One of them had a scar on his right cheek.
-Yes. The other one had long, dark hair.
-Scar...
SPA HISTORIC DRUGSTORE
Eight pharmacies in twenty days.
They make off with the pills, always.
Especially amphetamines.
And the money and the cash.
Yes. Also in Barcelona.
I suppose it's the thing to do now.
Hit the pharmacies, hmm?
It's like an epidemic.
And the M.O. is always the same.
A pregnant woman creates a diversion,
drawing attention,
then two or three men
get into the back room.
The boy. Don't forget.
-Yes, the boy.
-What boy?
There's this boy
who speaks Catalan who works with them.
Attracts the attention of the pharmacist,
makes sure the coast is clear.
Meanwhile, the others spring into action.
No, the descriptions don't match.
Not in all cases.
Maybe there are many of them.
They take turns.
But the pregnant woman and boy
are always there.
What are you trying to tell me?
That this is a gang?
I think it's obvious, no?
I don't know.
Around here, we've never had gangs before.
Well, now you do.
-This dance is called marinera.
-[MOTHER] And who is this Busquets?
Oriol. Oriol Busquets, from my class.
Ah, I don't know him.
You've never brought him home, have you?
Of course you don't know him.
I never bring anyone here.
-To them, we're just charnegos.
-Hey.
Don't talk like that. Your father is
a civil servant. We've been here years.
Yes, Mom. Whatever you say.
It's the first time I'm invited,
and I won't say no.
Done. There you go.
Well, I mean,
his mother could have phoned, right?
-[CHUCKLES]
-Why are you laughing?
Because we're a bit old
to ask for permission, Mom.
I don't know. Some people have made plans.
We're going on holidays in three days.
I'm not going to the village.
What? You're not coming?
Why should I? He won't even talk to me.
Well, what about when you get back?
You'll stay with your sister?
I'm better on my own.
Oh, no. No. That's not a good idea.
You stay with your sister.
-And you'll do whatever she says.
-Yeah, Mom. Okay.
Just go and don't worry.
It'll be good for us all.
[TRAIN RUMBLING]
-No way. Look who's there.
-What?
[BOY] Holy shit!
-Well, if it ain't our missing guy.
-That's right.
Where have you been?
-Around.
-What's with the bag?
Looks like he's off to the gym
to put on some muscle.
[LAUGHS] Yeah. Because right now.
-[NACHO GRUNTS]
-Hey. Take it easy, okay?
Cool it.
[HORN HONKS]
-[BOY 1] What's with them?
-[BOY 2] Are they calling us?
No. It's for me.
-You know these guys?
-A bit, yeah.
You know who they are?
[GRUNTS] Fuck!
-What the fuck was that?
-It's nothing. Leave me alone.
Fucking shit.
-[GUILLE] They're taking too long.
-[ZARCO] Lighten up. We're at the beach.
[GORDO] They'll bring cash. You'll see.
-Sure.
-Here they come.
[PIERNAS] Nice-looking gang.
-How's it going?
-Boys, show me what you got.
We sold three packets
to a couple of German girls.
[LAUGHS] Germans?
[LAUGHS MOCKINGLY]
-How did you talk to them?
-[DRÁCULA] Me?
Sign language.
Where there's a will, there's a way.
This is bullshit.
That's how things roll around here.
I mean, people, they're chill, you know?
Check out the brick I picked up.
[PIERNAS] Really good shit.
Nothing this good made it into the barrio.
[GUILLE] Jesus, what a bunch of idiots.
We're here to sell, and you buy instead?
-How much did you fork out?
-Two baggies.
Two baggies. Swear to God,
we're gonna lose money.
-You should listen to me.
-It's way too dangerous.
[GUILLE] It's not dangerous.
It's in and out. It's a bank.
That's where the money is.
We see the Gypsy
that buys from us and ask for guns.
No. I'm sick and tired of
this motherfucker taking us for a ride.
See those two?
Come with me.
We'll show these bozos how it's done.
[NACHO] Those girls
don't look like they do drugs.
-[ZARCO] Neither do you, and look at you.
-[ALL LAUGHING]
[GUILLE] This should be good.
-Roll us one. Let's try it.
-I sampled it and it's… [KISSES]
[GIRL SPEAKING FRENCH]
Hey there, girls. Got a light?
[GIRL CHUCKLES]
-Bonjour.
-Where are you from?
[BOTH SPEAKING FRENCH]
-They speak French.
-You speak French?
No, but it's a little bit like Catalan.
French it is.
I was in France once.
The village across the border.
-What's it called?
-Perpignan.
[GIRLS] Oui, Perpignan!
[GIRLS SPEAKING FRENCH]
-Help me out here. I'm clueless.
-Me too. They talk fast.
Check him out. He's talking a blue streak.
Hey, man. Kinda hot.
Yeah, but he can barely speak Spanish.
How can he talk to them?
-[PIERNAS] Look how close he is.
-[GORDO] Zarco is in his element.
What's he doing?
He says he's gonna
slip some pills to those two.
Zarco? Nah, he's gonna
slip them something else, real deep.
[MEN LAUGH]
They're students.
[BOTH GIRLS SPEAKING FRENCH]
And they wanna know what we do.
What we do? We do hits.
[GIRLS LAUGH]
-How do you say that?
-I have no idea.
Let's see if I can explain it to them.
[GIRL SPEAKING FRENCH]
Us? We rob pharmacies.
-[GORDO] Is it good?
-[GUILLE] Let me smoke it.
-[PIERNAS] It's a deal.
-[LINA] All right.
What are we doing here?
I wanna go to Gerona.
-Here we go.
-Let's see what happens first.
We're gonna wait for nothing.
[GORDO SCOFFS]
You're a wuss, you know that?
Hey, here they are.
All right, guys. Here's the deal.
Tonight, there's a party on the beach,
and the tourists are gonna be there.
-All right, my man!
-Make some dough!
Hey, ditch the long face.
Tonight, we're gonna move
a shit-load of dope.
[CHUCKLING]
-[CROWD CHEERING]
-[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
Hey, man, open wide.
What did I tell you?
This place is crawling with hippies.
We'll sell everything off, man.
[OVERLAPPING CHATTER, LAUGHTER]
All right.
[ZARCO] This one's for you.
Lina, don't sulk. It's just for tonight.
Do you want something? No?
["GET ON YOUR KNEES" BY CANARIOS PLAYING]
[ACCORDION MUSIC PLAYING]
Gafitas!
-Come here.
-What is it?
-I want you to meet a friend.
-No, not now.
Yes, you. I told her about the pills,
but I don't understand anything. Help me.
-[WOMAN SPEAKS IN GERMAN]
-[NACHO] Yes. We have drugs.
-[SPEAKS GERMAN]
-Yes, pills.
-[WOMAN SPEAKS GERMAN]
-Money? Okay.
What happened with the French girls?
Did you get anywhere?
Well, there was, uh, a lot of touching
and stuff, and then nothing.
-Nothing, huh?
-[DRÁCULA] Hey, we're in business!
-What?
-They're buying everything.
These two?
They're going back to Germany,
and they want as much as they can.
But do they have money?
They don't have pesetas,
but they have marks.
-What's a mark worth?
-A lot more than a peseta!
Thing is, we have to go to their place.
It's a campsite a few kilometers away.
-They're campers with money?
-[DRÁCULA] Yeah, man.
That's how these people roll.
Love, peace, and money.
-I'm gonna tell Zarco.
-No, he's busy.
Just tell him
we're leaving with these two,
and we're taking the Chrysler.
And you're coming.
-I'm not going.
-Who's gonna talk to these two?
[DRÁCULA] Leave him alone.
He's been smelling Tere's panties.
[NACHO] Go fuck yourself!
[DRÁCULA] Hey, don't get mad!
It's not gonna get you anywhere.
[VOCALIZING]
Tere.
Where's everybody?
Guille's doing some business.
The rest of them must be around.
Is Zarco gone too?
Not with them.
Maybe with the French girl.
I don't think so.
Come on, let's go find him.
Have you seen Zarco?
Haven't a fucking clue where he is.
[NACHO] We could go
where the cars are and wait there.
It'd be too bad, though.
It's kinda nice here.
No, I can't always run after him.
He's gonna show up.
Anyway, you're right.
It's kinda nice here.
[LAUGHS] Are you serious?
This is gonna do me a world of good.
And you too!
Wait for me!
Whoo!
[WATER SPLASHES]
[NACHO LAUGHS]
-It's cold, isn't it?
-[MOCKINGLY] "It's cold, isn't it?"
-No!
-What?
The bracelet.
-What? Did you lose it?
-My bracelet slipped off.
-Around here?
-Yeah, just now.
You got it.
You know something?
-What?
-You and I haven't fucked yet.
Are you nervous?
A bit.
[NACHO BREATHING HEAVILY]
[LOUD ROCK MUSIC PLAYING ON STEREO]
[GUILLE] I'm gonna be mad
if we get to the campsite
and they don't have money.
Ah, don't worry, man.
Right. If you ask me,
they just wanted a ride.
What are you doing?
Zarco left the tank almost empty.
We don't have enough to get there.
GAS STATION
GASOLINE
[MAN] Good evening.
Two thousand pesetas.
-Here you are.
-Thanks.
Have a good night.
Gimme the bag! Gimme the fucking bag!
-Hand it over. Don't try anything.
-Here. Take it.
Now, you're gonna stay right there.
Stay there.
Whatever you want.
[GUNSHOT]
[GUILLE MOANING]
[WOMAN SCREAMS]
Jesus! What the fuck did you do?
[WOMAN SCREAMING]
Fucking sons of bitches!
Bastards! Assholes!
-God, he shot me right through!
-What the fuck did you do, man?
[GUILLE] He shot me!
[GUILLE SCREAMS]
He shot me! He shot me!
-[WOMAN SCREAMING]
-Shut the fuck up!
I should have sliced
his motherfucking throat!
-Fucking hell!
-[SCREAMING]
Shut your fucking mouth! Shut the fuck up!
Let me go! Let me go!
Hey, you! Hey!
What are you doing? Get in the car!
[OVERLAPPING SHOUTING]
[WOMAN] Let me go!
-[CAR HONKS]
-Fucking shit!
[MAN 1] Yes, you can take him.
[MAN 2] Bring him over here.
[MAN 1] Be careful. Be careful.
[DRÁCULA GROANING]
[MAN 3] Easy now.
-Those are the pills, right?
-Yes. Over there.
There were four in the car, right?
Follow me.
[OFFICER] No rush for this one.
[TV playing faintly.
Good afternoon.
-Two beers, please.
-Make it just one.
Nothing. None of these people
were there with the kid.
Are you sure?
Yeah. Looks like they're still laying low.
They didn't even show up to the funeral.
They'll be laying low for a while.
And the one in the hospital?
You talk to the doctor?
He's too messed up. Can't count on him.
He'll pay for it.
Thank you.
You didn't ask to be assigned here, right?
No. I wanted Barcelona.
Ladies. How you doing?
It's obvious you don't partake.
I didn't like it either at first, really.
But then, you see, it kinda grew on me.
-And you're married?
-Mmm.
Yeah. I'm married.
In the end, we get these guys,
you'll have it easy.
Next year, I'll see you
at La Sagrada Familia.
-We'll see what happens if we catch them.
-Wait a second.
-I think we just got lucky.
-[CUENCA] Him?
[MAN] He's a big mouth.
He knows everybody.
You'll see. Come on.
Hey, Chino!
Who? Me?
Yeah. Don't play dumb. You saw me.
-I didn't do anything.
-I know. You're a real saint.
But listen to me for a sec. You, uh...
Shouldn't you be mourning
or something? Hmm?
Mourning what?
Well? The guy who died.
You two were very close, weren't you?
-Uh, Guille?
-Him, yeah.
Well, we weren't...
We weren't really friends, but I knew him.
Anyway, I'm sorry for your loss.
You have my sympathies, hmm?
Here's what I wanna know.
Guille, he was in on the pharmacies, no?
What pharmacies?
Fucking Chino.
I swear to God, you're asking for it.
I'm telling the truth.
I don't know about pharmacies.
You want another?
[KISSES HAND]
I swear on my life I'm not lying.
I haven't a clue. I don't know anything.
Empty your pockets. Show me what you got.
I don't have anything.
Chino, don't push me.
The next time I touch your face,
it's gonna be with my fist.
What's with you?
Didn't you wanna see how it's done here?
Something's gotta be done.
What's this shit?
Take out the rest. Come on.
-Wh-What?
-Turn around. Hands against the wall.
-I swear, I don't...
-Shut the hell up, you stupid moron.
Let's see what we've got here.
This ain't for a sore throat.
That's not mine.
Son of a bitch,
what are you talking about?
Are you saying I'm a liar? Hmm?
You're seeing this, right?
What should we do with him?
-Take him to the police station.
-Absolutely correct!
Bring him to the station.
Come on. If you weren't so stupid, Chino,
this wouldn't happen.
[PIERNAS] He's so cute in the picture.
And yet he was so ugly.
He had such a shitty temper.
Fuck this.
[ROCK MUSIC PLAYING ON RADIO]
-[NACHO] Cristina, there's nothing to eat.
-You should've bought something.
There's pasta and tomato sauce.
There you go. Pasta with tomato sauce.
[CRISTINA] You can boil water, can't you?
And then tidy up your room. It's a pigsty.
I'm fed up being the maid here.
-They're home next week. If they see this…
-Next week?
Time flies, doesn't it?
Yeah. Especially since
you're practically never here.
First you don't come home,
and then I couldn't
pry you out of bed with a crowbar.
Well, it's not like you haven't done
what you wanted.
You didn't think I'd notice your boyfriend
has been sleeping here every other night?
You better keep your mouth shut.
My lips are sealed.
Disgusting.
Yup, tastes like cardboard.
Hey, are you still hanging out
at the arcade?
Yeah, occasionally. Why?
Because Amparo told me
that someone robbed the place.
And apparently,
they stabbed the guy who works there.
-What, Mr. Tomàs?
-Well, I don't know his name.
And when did that happen?
Last night, I think. I said to myself,
"Thank goodness he hasn't left his room."
Weren't you helping him close sometimes?
[TELEPHONE RINGING]
Don't bother getting up, please.
Hello? Uh, yeah.
Yes, one second.
Nacho, it's for you.
Who is it?
Don't know. You have to go down.
Hey, Gafitas, why the long face?
Didn't you say we should lay low?
Yeah, I say a lot of things.
Get in. We're going for a ride.
Your place looks great.
-You guys have a bit of money.
-[IGNITION SPARKS]
What's your father do?
[ENGINE REVS]
-And yours?
-Mine? He scratches his balls.
You remember what a pain in the ass
Guille was about robbing a bank?
CENTRAL BANK
Are you serious?
Better than risking your life for peanuts
and end up getting shot in the back
at a gas station.
And the money for that?
The money came from the arcade.
If Guille had one of these,
he'd still be with us now.
We've been too stupid.
Now, you go in
and ask them to change this.
Find out how many people work in there,
where the safe is, all that stuff.
CENTRAL BANK
You want us to rob it on our own?
No. There'll be four of us.
Tere and I go in.
Gordo waits in the car
with the engine running.
And you on the corner,
watching out for the police.
CENTRAL BANK
Not again.
[GUARD] You can't park here.
-Manolo, come on.
-Don't "Manolo" me.
There's parking right over there.
-Just a couple minutes.
-We go through this every week, Pepín.
[MANOLO] Do I have to pick up boxes?
[PEPÍN] I'm going. I'm done.
Well, look at that. He's running.
Pepín is running!
[HAND TROLLEY CLANGING]
[MANOLO] Hurry up.
[PEPÍN] Yeah, I know.
[TERE] Move your ass!
Gimme that.
[ZARCO] You sure he saw us?
Yes, I'm sure.
Maybe he didn't realize.
With two guns and stocking on your heads?
He'd have to be fucking stupid!
This is bullshit! We got almost nothing.
Did you see the cashier's face?
-I swear the guy was shitting himself.
-Yeah, man.
[GUNSHOT]
-[TERE YELPS]
-[ZARCO] Jesus Christ! What the fuck?
-Where did they come from?
-I don't have a fucking clue!
-[ZARCO] Fuck!
-Oh, God.
[GUN COCKS]
[TERE YELPS]
[ZARCO] Come on, Gafitas!
Take it. Come on.
-[NACHO PANTING]
-[ZARCO] Fucking shit!
[GORDO] Come on, Gafitas.
Shoot, for fuck's sake!
Fuck!
[INTENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[GRUNTS]
[SINGER VOCALIZING]
[GENTLE, PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYS]
[ZARCO SIGHS]
Fucking Gordo. He snores like an old lady.
[NACHO CHUCKLES]
Didn't even notice.
You did good yesterday.
You got some balls.
Do you think he's dead?
I don't know.
Hope he's not.
But we'll have to be careful for a while.
If I were you, I wouldn't go to La Font.
I mean, do what the hell you wanna do.
But that's my advice. Stay away.
But why?
Because you're not like us.
-I do the same as you.
-Yeah.
You do, but it's different.
I don't understand.
You got something to lose,
and we don't.
You have another life.
But I want this life.
You know what it's like in prison?
Because I spent six months there,
and I'm telling you, it's no fucking joke.
-Even less for someone like you.
-Why? Because I don't have the balls?
No, man. It's not a matter of balls.
You've seen what you had to see.
From now on,
everything is the same or worse.
This isn't gonna end well.
Man, I'm freezing.
You really like Tere, don't you?
Yeah, she's cool.
You like to fuck her.
I mean, like at the beach the other day.
Did you think I wouldn't find out?
[BELL TOLLING]
[BAND PLAYING]
Excuse me, I'm looking for a girl.
Tall, with black hair. Her name's Tere.
One street over.
That house is full of kids.
-Thank you.
-Sure.
[TINNY POP SONG PLAYING ON RADIO]
Hello.
I'm looking for Tere.
Tere.
-What do you want?
-To talk to you.
-Has something happened?
-No.
Well, I don't know.
I haven't been to La Font in days.
Why are you here?
No reason.
It's strange to see you like this.
What do you want? Why are you here?
-Have you talked to Zarco?
-About what?
About me.
-Why should we talk about you?
-Well…
[NACHO CLEARS THROAT]
You guys have no secrets, right?
You told him what happened at the beach.
I didn't tell him anything.
What are you trying to say?
The other day, he talked to me.
Told me not to go back to La Font
and that I should stay away from you guys.
Yeah.
I wanted to know what you think.
What do you want me to say?
Do what you want.
You must have an opinion.
Or you don't care
if you never see me again?
Zarco said that 'cause he's your friend
and doesn't want you to get hurt.
Yeah.
Because of that,
and he doesn't like that you and I...
You and I what?
Shit, Tere. What are you playing at?
I'm here because of you.
And I want to know...
What? If we're gonna fuck again?
You only did it with me
to get back at Zarco, right?
You saw him with the French girl
and you thought, "I'll show him."
You don't understand.
You're the one who doesn't understand.
Nacho.
Of course I'd care
if I never saw you again. A lot.
But I don't know, you have your life.
You've gotta live it.
You should know that.
[WOMAN] Tere!
Come on, get back here.
Day after tomorrow,
we're all going to La Font.
But in case I don't see you…
[TENDER GUITAR MUSIC PLAYS]
Goodbye, Gafitas.
-[WOMAN] Tere!
-I'm coming.
[BAR PATRONS CHATTERING]
One of the ones that went in was a girl,
and the street cop who warned us saw
a 16-year-old boy
on the street on lookout.
-Yeah, like at the pharmacy.
-Exactly.
But I still don't understand
why you're convinced they're the same.
-[COLETTE] A bit more?
-No, I'm fine.
Whatever you say.
If we show this
to the provincial commissioner,
we're screwed.
We're talking to someone
who knows them well.
Yesterday, he heard the girlfriend
of one of them named Gordo say
that they shot a cop.
But that thank God he wasn't dead.
Miraculously.
His helmet stopped the bullet.
Otherwise, he'd be in a wooden box
with his brains scattered
all over the road.
Sons of bitches.
Then let's go after them.
A beer, please.
What's up, man?
I haven't seen you in a while.
I was away.
You haven't heard the news, then?
-What news?
-About Piernas.
Cops picked him up yesterday.
They say... they say he was involved
in the bank robbery. Was it in Bordils?
But he wasn't there.
Oh, no. He wasn't there.
Hey there, Gafitas.
I just heard about Piernas.
-It sucks big-time.
-Yeah. Especially now.
-I'll be right back.
-All right.
Hey, Rata. What are you up to?
Not much.
[CHINO] Hey, why don't you take me?
Take you? Where?
Wherever you're planning to go.
You know, I'm, uh... I'm up for anything.
[GORDO] Yeah, whatever, Chino.
You, outside. Getting hot in here.
Now, where the fuck is Tere?
If you're looking
for someone else, I'll go.
No, the place is huge.
We need three of us.
Exactly. You behind the wheel,
Tere, Zarco, and I.
-[WOMAN] Carlos!
-It's gonna get messed up.
We gotta pick up the car, drive over,
and do it while it's still a good time.
There you are. Thank God.
-You turned up.
-Yeah. I came.
[GORDO] What about Rata?
He just got out.
He doesn't want any trouble.
[GORDO] Ah, shit.
The four of us can do it, right?
[ZARCO] We need one more.
-[GORDO] What about Chino?
-Nah, I don't trust him with a gun.
[GORDO] He can drive.
And me?
You keep watch.
-I'm going in too.
-There's no more guns.
-Then you can stay outside.
-No.
I'm going in.
You asked him to come.
Well, that's how it is.
-Good day, ma'am. How are you today?
-Very well.
Yes, that'll do.
[CLERK] Here you are.
[ZARCO] Okay, people.
Everybody on the fucking ground!
On the ground!
[GORDO] The fucking ground!
[PATRONS CLAMORING]
On the fucking ground! Nobody move!
You, get up.
[GORDO] Face down!
Get the fuck up right now, bastard!
Open the door, or I blow his head off!
-I said open the fucking door, right now!
-Move!
-[ZARCO] Do it now!
-Or I shoot him!
[LOUD RATTLING]
JUAN'S BARBERSHOP
TELEPHONE
[TENSE GUITAR MUSIC PLAYS]
Open it up, motherfucker. This way!
-Come on!
-[GORDO] On the fucking ground!
Hey, on the ground. You, face down!
[NACHO] Anybody move, and we'll shoot you.
On the ground. Don't move!
Drop that right now, you bastard!
Get the fuck up.
Get up, I said. Open the safe.
-I can't.
-Open the fucking safe!
-It has a time delay. I can't open it.
-What?
-We have to wait ten minutes...
-Like hell we do! Open it, motherfucker!
Two, four…
[MUTTERING QUIETLY]
[LINE RINGING]
[DISCONNECT TONE DRONES]
Come on, piece of shit!
[ZARCO] Come on, hurry up!
I haven't got all fucking day.
-There it is.
-Come on. Move over there.
Hey, you!
Get back with the others right now.
Get over there.
On the ground! On the fucking ground!
[GORDO] Don't you fucking move from there!
[PATRON WHIMPERING]
SNACK BAR ISAMA
Gimme a line.
Where the fuck is Zarco?
-What the fuck are you doing?
-Gotta wait for the safe.
-How long?
-Four more minutes. Gimme that.
-No fucking way! We gotta go!
-We're gonna wait.
-We gotta go.
-There's fuck-all here! We're gonna wait!
Hey, uh, Cuenca.
I, uh... I need to speak with
Inspector Cuenca.
[MAN] I'm going to ask you…
[PRISONER GURGLING]
…one last fucking time.
[PIERNAS GASPING FOR BREATH]
[GRUNTS IN PAIN]
Tell me who the fuck
was with you at the bank.
[DOOR OPENS]
-[MAN 2] Cuenca, phone call.
-Shut the fucking door!
You, look at me.
Come on, man.
Son of a bitch.
Hello?
We're gonna get busted. Come on.
You, come here. Open the door.
Do it right now.
Where the fuck are you going?
I told you not to move!
-How much longer?
-Twenty seconds.
Get back over here, you son of a bitch.
Don't you fucking move!
-Hurry up!
-It's opening.
All right, get out of the way.
Move to the fucking corner.
[CHINO] They're still inside. Yeah. Yeah.
Dirty fucking snitch! You piece of shit!
Let's go.
-Come on!
-Come on, let's hurry!
-[ALARM RINGING]
-[ZARCO] Come on!
Where are they?
Where's Chino? Fucking hell!
[ZARCO] The fuck is this shit?
Where is she? We can't leave without Tere.
-Tere knows how to take care of herself.
-Come on.
There she is! Gordo, there she is!
-Wait up.
-[SIREN WAILS]
[GORDO] No fucking way!
[INTENSE ROCK MUSIC PLAYING]
Shit! What do we do?
[ZARCO] Floor it!
Come on, man. Faster. We gotta lose them.
Motherfuckers.
They're closing in. Step on it.
Zarco, what do we do?
Pass the arch. Turn right.
[GORDO] Fucking shit!
[ZARCO] Keep going!
[PASSERBY YELLS]
[GORDO] Shit!
-[ZARCO] Fucking hell.
-[NACHO] Faster!
-Look out!
-Shut up!
[NACHO] Gordo!
-[TRUCK HORN BLARES]
-Oh, fuck!
[GORDO] Oh, God.
-[SIRENS WAILING]
-Come on, Gordo, step on it.
-[OFFICER] They're heading towards Gerona.
-Roger. They're coming.
They'll come in over La Barca bridge.
[SIREN WAILS]
Come on, Gordo.
They're closing in. Faster, faster!
You're gonna get us killed, man!
POLICE
[HELICOPTER WHIRRING OVERHEAD]
-[OFFICER] They're coming in.
-Almost here.
I can't believe this shit.
Fuck!
Come on, Gordo. Go back quick! Come on!
Fire!
[ZARCO] Come on!
[EXCLAIMS IN PAIN]
Right in the fucking ear!
-Zarco, are you okay?
-I'm fine!
Keep going, Gordo!
[CUENCA] Come on, move it!
Holy shit! Fuck! Shit!
Son of a bitch.
Careful, the road is closed. Brake, Gordo!
[ZARCO] Let's go! Come on, Gordo!
Fuck! Hurry up!
-[ZARCO] Let's go! Move!
-[GORDO] Fucking hell!
[ZARCO] Hurry up!
Run, run!
[NACHO CRIES OUT]
-[GRUNTS]
-Fucking shit!
Come on, get up!
Come on, come on!
-Get up! Run!
-Shit! Fuck!
-Bastards!
-Sons of bitches!
[ZARCO] Watch yourself!
Fuck, they're there!
Fucking assholes!
It's just a scratch.
[NACHO GRUNTING, GROANING]
Fucking hell!
Gordo, we gotta go now!
[GORDO YELLING]
[GORDO CRYING OUT]
Gordo, no!
No! No! Fuck!
You fucking bastards!
Fucking bastards!
Come on, we gotta go!
[NACHO GROANING]
Come on, hurry up!
[GRUNTS IN PAIN]
[GRUNTING]
Ah, my leg! Fucking hell!
-[YELLS]
-We gotta keep going!
-I can't fucking walk.
-Yes, you can!
-No, I can't fucking walk.
-You get away!
-You can! We gotta keep going!
I'm telling you,
get the fuck away from me or you're dead!
Get away from me right now!
[PANTING]
[BELL TOLLING]
[MOTHER] Cristina, help me put this away.
[CRISTINA] Yeah, I'm coming.
-[GASPS] Nacho!
-It's nothing.
-Nacho, what happened to you?
-I fell off the bike.
-You're covered in blood!
-It looks worse than it is.
[OVERLAPPING CLAMORING]
It looks bad, but it's nothing.
Don't worry.
He fell off the motorbike.
We have to take him to the hospital!
-Don't worry.
-Where's the first-aid kit?
In the bedroom.
-[MOTHER] Oh, my God!
-It's nothing, Dad.
Let's see what you've done. The kit, Rosa.
[ROSA WHIMPERING]
Mom, I mean it. It's nothing.
It looks worse than it is.
Take off your shirt.
-Right. Thank...
-Here.
-You two, out.
-All right. Mom, come here.
-I've got this.
-[CRISTINA] It's no big deal.
It's okay, Mom.
-Right. Let me have a look.
-I'm telling you, it's just a scratch.
This isn't from a motorbike.
Will you tell me the truth?
I was on the bike and I fell off.
Ignacio, If you want my help,
you have to tell me the truth.
If you don't,
you can leave this house right now.
[SNIFFS]
-[NACHO CRYING]
-What happened, son? What's wrong?
[CRYING]
[SHEEP CLAMORING]
[MAN ON TV] Watch out for the wolf!
The wolf!
They didn't send me documents.
I was waiting for them to vote.
[MAN 1] For the election,
I voted for
Pacte Democràtic per Catalunya,
as my father voted,
as did my grandfather before him…
[VEHICLE APPROACHING]
Nacho.
-[WOMAN] I voted for the Communist Party.
-[MAN 2] The Communist Party?
[CAR DOORS OPENING, CLOSING]
[PEOPLE CONTINUE SPEAKING ON TV]
[KNOCKING AT DOOR]
Good evening. Ignacio Cañas?
-That's me.
-[CUENCA] We need to talk to your son.
-Is he with you?
-Yes, he's here with me.
Come in.
Nacho's already in bed.
Isn't it a bit early?
Um, yes. We had
a little fishing accident earlier today.
[MAN] Hmm.
You like to fish, huh?
Very much.
We've been going out to sea all week.
All week? But this isn't your house.
No, it's a friend's.
He's back in Gerona.
And since we had
a few days of vacation left...
-My wife gave you the address, right?
-Yes, yes.
Yeah, she did. But listen, this, uh...
This little accident, how did...
Nacho got scratched by the hook
while casting the line.
A bit dramatic, nothing more.
We didn't even go to the doctor.
I tended to it myself.
Can you tell him we're here?
Yeah, sure.
But what is this about?
Why do you want to see my son?
We have evidence
that your son took part in a bank robbery.
We're taking him
to the station for questioning.
That can't be. Impossible.
-Must be a mistake.
-Go get him.
-N-No, wait...
-You stay here.
-No, I don't understand...
-Easy.
Calm down.
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
There he is.
Come on. Wake up, Gafitas.
That's what your friends call you, right?
[DOOR CLOSES]
This whole fishing thing…
[CUENCA CHUCKLES]
The vacation.
Let's forget about it.
I know you want to help your son,
but a false testimony
could land you in jail too.
Wouldn't be the first time.
I spent 48 hours in a cell many years ago
for taking part
in a student demonstration.
My father bailed me out, and I was freed.
When we got home,
he had a police file with him.
It was mine.
On it, it was written,
"Hostile to the regime."
With that, I could've never had
a job in the public administration.
I dunno what life would have been like,
but it would have been very different.
He bribed a cop?
He gave him his watch,
at the risk of ending up in jail himself,
just to give me a fighting chance.
-If you're thinking of offering me money...
-I'm telling you to do what you have to.
If you want to accuse me
of something, do it,
but I will still say
that I've been here all week with my son,
and that we've been fishing.
Your son has
committed a crime and has to pay.
The law applies to everyone.
-Life is not the same for everyone.
-[SIGHS]
My son stands a good chance. He has me.
-He has his mother and his sister.
-You'll be there when he gets out.
We will, but he won't.
He would never be the same,
and you know that.
Hidalgo!
-[DOOR OPENS]
-[HIDALGO] What?
-How much longer?
-Just a sec. He's coming his hair.
[DOOR CLOSES]
We have time.
Want to change your statement?
Your son will confess.
Perhaps he's already done so.
Why make matters worse?
We were here all day together.
Fishing.
[HIDALGO] We don't have all day.
[HIDALGO] Hurry up.
The owner of the house,
who you got the key from.
Does he know?
[DOOR OPENS]
He's a friend of yours?
-You told him everything?
-Yes.
[HIDALGO] Took forever
to put the T-shirt on the kid.
It's all right. We won't take him in.
It's not him.
-What?
-[CUENCA] You heard him before.
They've been here all week, fishing.
You kidding, right?
Nope.
You said the owner of the house
came here yesterday.
He left this morning and even offered
to take the boy to the hospital in Gerona.
Yes. He said, well,
since he had to go back…
-Are you sure?
-Yes.
You're sure if we ask your friend
for a statement, that's what he'll say?
Exactly, in those words.
Yes. Of course.
Yes.
You see? It's not him.
[HIDALGO SIGHS]
Hey, Cuenca.
You made the right call.
What matters is we nabbed Zarco.
These folks are normal. [LAUGHS]
The poor kid was so scared, I tell you,
he wouldn't last
three months at the Modelo.
[GUARD] Ignacio Cañas?
Ignacio Cañas Navarro?
Yes, that's me.
Sorry.
[INDISTINCT, OVERLAPPING CHATTER]
[CHATTER GROWS MUFFLED]
What's up, Gafitas?
[CHUCKLES]
Shit, you're a gentleman.
-How are you, Zarco?
-Fucked.
Especially my teeth.
Any day now, I'll pull them out.
Fuck it. They feed us shit anyway.
Yeah. Hey, I know a couple
of your clients, you know.
-Do you?
-The Lemon, the Colombian,
and Yuri, the fucking Ruskie.
They all say you're great.
I can't be all that good if they're here.
If you worked miracles,
you'd be a priest, not a lawyer.
[CHUCKLES]
Well, I've known for a few months
that you've been sent here.
I should have come earlier. I'm sorry.
Don't worry about it.
The main thing is you're here.
Shit, Gafitas.
It's been so many fucking years.
Twenty-eight.
-What have you been doing all this time?
-Oh, not too much.
Well, what did you do after your studies?
-Did you marry?
-Yes, but it didn't last long. Two years.
-Kids?
-No.
Not that you know of, at least.
No, no, no, no, no. I'm totally sure.
Hey, um, I've been
going through your file…
-Hmm.
-…and, um, it won't be easy.
We should try to unify the charges,
-and if we're lucky, in a few years...
-A few years.
I don't think I have a few years.
Yeah, okay. We can try another angle.
Seeking released for medical reasons...
Hey, she sent you
a letter too, didn't she?
Tere? Yes.
That's why you're here.
She told you to come.
The bitch.
She told me to call you.
She always cared about you.
Her whole life.
Do you know,
she never missed a monthly visit?
It didn't matter where I was.
She'd travel all through Spain.
800 kilometers when I was in Cádiz.
And then one day,
she didn't show up. Ah, God.
A shudder ran down my spine.
The damn disease took her, just like that!
I was at the funeral.
It was well-attended.
She was well-loved in her neighborhood.
I should have been there too,
but these fucking bastards...
And you, asshole,
with the lousy life you had,
-it never occurred to you to reach her?
-You don't think I never thought of it?
-I thought of it a million times.
-And you didn't.
No. Zarco, I never stood a chance.
She'd always be hooked on you,
even as you were rotting in here.
Yeah. You'd have liked it better
if it had been me that day.
What?
Come on, man. If I'd gotten shot that day,
you'd have had free rein.
What are you talking about?
You saved me that day.
Well, yes.
I've thought about it. I can't lie to you.
I'm quite the piece of shit.
-[CHUCKLES]
-What's so funny, huh?
You got it all wrong, Gafitas.
-She was crazy about you.
-[SCOFFS]
Yeah, right. Let's leave it at that.
She never told you?
That she was crazy about me? No.
She was my sister.
Of course she never told you.
She was too embarrassed.
-Your sister?
-Mmm.
Same father, different mother.
Nobody knew in our barrio.
Not even us, at first.
But of course, when things got serious,
her mother told her,
just in case I knocked her up.
But we never did...
But you meant everything to her.
-She was my sister.
-She meant everything to you.
She was my fucking sister!
Anyway, what does it matter?
The past is the past.
It's better to forget what could've been.
[TENDER GUITAR MUSIC PLAYING]
[CAR HORN HONKS]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
[TINNY POP MUSIC PLAYING]
Hi. Have you seen Jou?
Jou? No, I haven't seen him
in about six months.
[NACHO] Yeah.
Where's the cigarette machine?
There.
CIGARETTES
What's up, Gafitas?
Tere.
Long time no see.
A whole year.
At least.
It's good to see you.
What are you up to?
Studying. And you?
Well, I do what I can, as usual.
And I help my sister.
She's pregnant again.
-You serious?
-My sister's something else.
And Zarco?
Still inside. I visit him every month.
Hasn't been tried yet?
No, but it's getting complicated,
because he got into a fight in jail
and they added a charge.
Yeah.
But you know how he is.
He complains a lot, but hangs in there.
[CHUCKLES]
You want a drink?
I can't. They're waiting for me.
Who? Your girlfriend?
No, some friends.
But you do have a girl?
No girlfriend.
Not one in particular.
You sure know how to get around, Gafitas.
Anyway, maybe you can help me.
I was looking for Jou to get some.
Oh, well, he got busted a while ago.
How much do you want?
Two dimes. [CHUCKLES]
-All right. Wait outside. I'll fix you up.
-Okay.
[PASSERSBY CHATTERING]
There you go. Thanks.
-Thanks.
-See ya.
[DOOR SWINGS OPEN]
It'd be nice to meet up
a little longer sometime.
Yeah. We, uh... we should get together.
You're so beautiful.
Is that what you say to that girl?
No. I don't tell her that.
Not yet.
All right, we should do it, then.
I'm going dancing tomorrow.
The Rufus?
If you wanna join me...
Sure.
See you tomorrow at the Rufus.
For sure?
For sure.
Well, just in case…
Goodbye, Gafitas.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[TENDER GUITAR MUSIC PLAYING]
[SINGER SINGING GENTLE BALLAD IN SPANISH]
[ENERGETIC ROCK SONG IN SPANISH PLAYS]